Chapter 1429:
In Modern Day (27)

“…” For a moment, I’m at a loss on how to respond to Anderson Hood. I’m afraid that I would end up quarreling with him the moment I open my mouth.

After a few seconds, I finally find a relatively euphemistic solution.

“Oh, you’re even able to paint?”

The receptionist eagerly says, “Heh, he knows a lot of things. He originally came to our country to learn banter, claiming that he’s proficient in all kinds of things.”

That sounds like sarcasm… The receptionist and this foreign teacher don’t seem to be on good terms… I wonder if he’s speaking the truth or just joking… Although I’m not particularly good at observing people, his behavior is a little obvious.

“Haha, if you wish to learn banter, I can teach you as well,” Anderson Hood says with a well-enunciated Chinese accent.

“We’ll see?” I’m a little confused about the current situation, and I have no choice but to say something perfunctory like “I’ll check my schedule.”

After watching Anderson walk into the office, I turn my head and ask the male receptionist, “Can I not sign up for his class?”

“That’s one of your rights.” The male receptionist looks excited. “A wise choice!”

He then gives me a thumbs up.

“Th-This… foreign teacher—Anderson… Is he that bad?” I glance in the direction of the office.

The male receptionist chuckles.

“To be honest, he’s very capable. His only flaw is…”

He pauses.

“What is it?” I can’t help but ask in response.

The male receptionist turns solemn.

“That he’s not a mute!”

“Hahaha.” I laugh, half-sincere and half-polite.

Then, I ask curiously, “Do people sign up for his classes?”

“Yes, quite a lot.” The male receptionist curls his lips.

“Aren’t they aware that you can’t withdraw from classes and switch teachers after signing up?” I take the opportunity to gather more details.

“No.” The male receptionist quickly corrects me. “We have one trial lesson. If you’re not satisfied, you can switch to another teacher.”

He pauses and laughs.

“Well, you know, some people just like to get mocked and trampled on.”

It sounds like they have a special fetish… I stop asking further.

“Then I’ll sign up for your principal’s class. Are there weekend classes?”

“Yes.” The male receptionist quickly does the introductions.

I don’t waste any time. After paying 6,666 yuan, I sign up for the Dream Tutoring Classes’ weekend business English class.

After leaving the Dream Tutoring Classes, I don’t leave the building. Instead, I find a quiet corner and take in the feel of the air conditioner. I then make a record of today’s events.

To be a commercial spy, one has to act like a commercial spy. I have to live up to Miss Huang’s payment!

Done! I casually tap my phone and look at the department chat to prevent myself from missing any important notices.

Luo Shan: “Take note, take note: CEO Huang is bringing a VIP over to visit. Everyone, please be more professional.”

VIP… Oh, that client named Zarathushtra. Heh heh, I actually missed him again. Looks like we aren’t fated to meet… I hold my phone and consider what to do next.

It’s rare for me to have free time in the afternoon on a non-weekend day. I can’t waste it.

Hmm, I’ll go catch a movie. There shouldn’t be a lot of people at this time. With that thought in mind, I immediately head to the larger mall next door. Then, I take the elevator to the fourth floor and start searching for the cinema.

Eh, there’s a signing event… Looking around, I see many people lining up at the entrance of a large bookstore.

It’s obvious that a famous author is here to do a fansigning event.

With some level of curiosity, I deliberately pass by and see a few poster stands.

Romance Queen… Slacker Without a Dream… This pen name, heh, the authors nowadays really have weird pen names… I don’t know the author of the fansign event, nor do I have any intention of joining in the fun.

Of course, I’m still a little curious as to what the author looks like. After all, the few poster stands that aren’t blocked mainly introduced the Romance Queen’s new book without any pictures.

I’ll come take a look after the movie… I mutter to myself and follow the road signs to the other side of the mall. At the end of the road, I find the cinema.

Because I haven’t thought of what to watch, I stay in the lobby and look for something that piques my interest from the promotional pictures.

Suddenly, I feel the light in front of me dim.

A tall man appears beside me!

He’s so tall. He’s almost two meters… I look at him from the corner of my eye and realize that he looks like a basketball player.

Wait, he seems to be wearing the junior high school uniform near my neighborhood!

Holy sh*t, he’s only in middle school and he’s already two meters tall?

What do children nowadays eat?

A-And he dyed his hair brownish-yellow…

Does he need to attend classes? Well, it’s summer vacation now.

But why are you wearing your school uniform during the summer vacation?

As I lampoon, I take a stealthy step in the opposite direction, in case the child makes me look like a dwarf.

Meanwhile, I find the movie that I’ll be watching. I don’t have to wait too long.

“The Great Pirate 3: Crazy Adventurer”

In the corresponding promotional pictures, a man in a top hat and trench coat is standing between lightning, waves, and storms with three retro pirate ships surrounding him. And at the bow of each ship stands a beautiful female pirate.

Multi-Character Audio Drama - Special Episode:
Klein’s Niece

Note: This is a non-canon special episode of Lord of Mysteries released on May 28th, 2021 on Himalaya Audio Book APP. It is translated by Windvally.

Klein’s Niece POV:

Today, I greeted Mr. Fool~

I told Dakye about this, but he didn’t believe me.

I wasn’t lying to him though. ヽ(ಠ_ಠ) ノ

Ah!

That’s right!

At the time, why did I not tell him what Mr. Fool looked like?

He has……scribbling noise

He……has……scribbling noise

Eh? The ink ran out? scribbling noise

Huh, it’s working again~ (^.^)

scribbling noise

Anyways, Dakye is a big dummy!

All he does is reciting weird poem lines.

The book he lent me last time, <The World’s World>, was not enjoyable to read in the slightest!

disappointed humpfh

Forget it! I will listen to auntie, from now on I will never bring this up with someone else again, that I’ve met Mr. Fool.

Today’s dinner, we are having Mr. Fool’s holy meal.

That’s what father said: “This is a holy meal.”

But aren’t these type of food what we normally have in our family anyways?

Ummh……

Lamb boiled with soft tofu.

Beef soup.

Mashed potato.

Fried Tussock fish.

Stewed rhubarb.

giggles There’s also sweet ice tea!

Sweet ice tea taste so delicious~ ԅ(♡﹃♡ԅ)

Mmh……After we finished the holy meal, my father was once again busy discussing about curly baboons. He won’t play with me.

Uhm……That’s why, I am not telling him ~

~ that I had ice cream this morning!

Mmh, the little big brother who gifted me ice cream was really nice.

Mmh~~~ hiccup

Mmh…I am really full.

Auntie said, if I pray to Mr. Fool before I go to sleep, there will be angels descending into my dream world and giving me good dreams.

Mmh, Mr. Fool is so great! I have decided to give this a try.

scribbling noise

It’s a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Fool.

Have a good night!

closing diary noise

Side Story:
Rebellious Teenager

Note: It was published as an exclusive side story of Lord of Mysteries in the “Taiwanese Physical Book, Lord of Mysteries 01: Commission of Gold Pound” that covers from Web Novel Chapter 213: Another Look to Chapter 242: Bakerland.

This is a Bullet Point Paraphrasing Summary by Windvally, not the complete translation of the story.

Intis Southern Region, The Town of Nosil.

[Another beautiful day is about to beginning.]

Danitz said as he smiled at his friends around him. He is currently sitting atop metal fences situated near the edge of the town.

[A beautiful day!]

His friends shouted loudly, appearing very energetic.

For teens like them, their clothing isn’t exactly the best in quality, but most definitely trendy, their choices closely resembles the current tending styles of Trier.

Of course, they were only following, but not matching, because there’s a very big difficulty that’s preventing them from doing so - No money!

Bullet Point Summary to Skip some segments:

After goofing with friend for the whole day, Danitz went back to him.
His father tried to beat him, but he dodges skillfully, never got hit once, and his father is dead tired and angry.
Parents stated he’s 16 now and needs to take up responsibilities. They talked with the servant head working for the owner of a grape farm in the town. Danitz could be an apprentice servant.
Danitz wants to go to Trier and be rich
The next day Danitz slipped out of home before his parents could catch him.
He met up with his friends told him a new group of sailors and a bard arrived at the town’s local bar.
They went to the bar together.

The town’s bar almost have no interior decorations, only the wall was painted, and a few pictures cut from old magazines and newspapers were plastered on the wall.

At the bar counter, above the alcohol shelf, hanged the head of a giant snake, already white and cleaned to the bone.

That empty eye socket, is large enough to swallow the mouth of a normal adult, causing every drunkard who visits this bar to lower their head unconsciously when meeting its eyes.

Danitz was no exception.

According to what he knew, this giant snake skull was brought back from the Southern Continent by this bar’s owner. It’s that man’s souvenir for remembering many years of adventure.

That’s also why, even though this mister is rather quiet and introverted, no one dares to have greedy thoughts about his bar.

Even if a mafia from the big cities come to this place, when they see that giant snake skull, that owner’s ridiculous and exaggeratedly muscular arms, legs, and just muscle in general, most would probably wisely choose to interact peacefully. After all, a small town’s bar isn’t exactly that profitable, it’s not worth the trouble.

Danitz was always a little disappointed by this.

It’s not that he wanted a fellow native to be bullied, but rather he desired to witness how strong the bar owner is, as someone who used to work as a mercenary and adventurer on the Southern Continent.

In a way, the owner could be counted as a legendary person of the small town of Nosil. No competition within the past 30 years at the very least.

He left this place at a very young age, headed towards the Southern Continent for adventure. Around his middle age, he returned to his home town, carrying with him a decent fortune, a body of muscle, and a giant snake skull. He opened up a bar, married a widow, and had a kid.

He stayed absolutely silent in regards to his nearly 20+ years of adventurous life on the Southern Continent. No matter who asked, he only responded with unimportant things to change the subject.

Danitz was very disappointed by this.

However, Danitz once heard from a friend who live close to the bar owner, that the man will always do one of two things every single night: He either drink until it’s nearly morning before dropping, or fuck his wife until very very late into the night.

He seemed to be afraid of entering sleep.

If I have a beautiful wife, I will also screw her up and down until late into the night…Dantiz mumbled to himself in a low voice, while keeping an eye out for the sailors his friend mentioned.

Bullet Point Summary to Skip some segments:

They mingled and drank with the sailors, acting like kids pretending to be mafia adults.
The sailors are friendly, here in town only to stock up on wine and fresh water.
They told Danitz and his friend about the life of a secret-treasure hunter on the sea.
They told the story of a ship called [Laurel Flower].
[About 100 years ago, Leon Kingdom had a ship called Laurel Flower. It was filled with old, jewelry, and valuables they ransacked from the Southern Continent. It strayed off course and sank to the bottom at a location somewhere in the Berserk Sea and Sonia Sea. Finding it means obtaining things that can sell for a couple billion Verl Gold.]

The young adult sailor who’s now drunk with a rather red face, looked around at these teenagers listening to his stories and laughed.

[Just that much money was able to surprise all of you? There are many more legends on the seas.]

[At a certain location on the Berserk Sea, the treasure of The God of Death is waiting. It is waiting for a person with a very specific, special key to open it. And that person? He will become the new God of Death….On the seas, every single individual is chasing after the [Fountain of Youth], just one single sip from it, will grant a person eternal youth.Not only will he never growing old ever again, but he will also become extremely powerful…]

At this point, the bard who traveled here along with the sailors started playing his lyre:

[They raised their head and looked at the sky, that fire like cloud looked like a seas of crimson, wide and glittering.]

[They looked down at the ocean, reflections of light scattered forth, a round bright moon is rising from the surface of the sea.]

[They walked across flat yet harden surface of sand]

[They walked into caves corroded by years of rain and wind]

[It’s like a home delicately designed just for them, there are halls, gem filled ceilings, and living rooms…] (Altered from a irl poem)

Bullet Point Summary to Skip some segments:

Danitz asked the guy if he can be a treasure hunter too. The guys told him to grow more muscle first. And stated pure treasure hunters are a rare sight, as most are also pirates on the side.
Danitz isn’t giving up and is angry. When these people are done drinking, as soon as they turned around a corner out of Danitz sight, he gave them a middle finger and said Dogshit!
As Danitz is about to leave the closing bar, he passed by the bar owner who is about to close the front door. The bar owner slowly said in a very deep voice:
[Never go onto the sea.]
Danitz was stunned for a second, and looked towards the bar owner with unfocused eyes. The bar owner stood still in the dim environment, neither his eyes nor his facial expressions were definable in the darkness. With a bam, the owner closed the door, blocking Danitz’s view of him.
Danitz stayed home the next morning, not wanting to meet his friends, as he’s unsure if his friend heard the sailors rejecting his question of becoming a treasure hunter.
For a teenager, saving face, his self-esteem is perhaps even more important than his life!
His father was angry, guessing that he probably went to goof at the bar yesterday.
His father told him that the sailors was only able to carry part of their wine and water cargo with them. The grape farm owner still need to send the rest of the goods to Sali Port for the sailors.
His parents used their connection and some money to get this job for Danitz. Knowing that he would use this chance to do what he always wanted to do. They love him after all.
His father told Danitz [Do not die out there.]
Dantiz was excited. He’s going to have leave right now.

[He said he doesn’t want to come out and see you, because he will get angry every time he sees you.]

Danitz’s mother said while wiping away some tears on the corner of her eyes.

Danitz cursed that stubborn old man with a few sentence inside his heart, he hugged his mother, and turned around to walk towards the waiting caravans.

As the caravans started moving, after traveling about 10-20 meters, Dantiz turned his head around unconsciously, his old man was standing next to his mother, not knowing when he already came out.

A bright smile appeared on Danitz’s face, he waved his right hand at them, and shouted silently inside his heart:

[Father, Mother, I will return after becoming rich!]

Chapter 1:
Crimson

Ouch!

It hurts so much!

My head is killing me!

The bizarre dream filled with murmurs shattered instantly. Zhou Mingrui, still asleep, felt a throbbing pain in his head as if someone had hit him with a pole—again and again. No, it was more like a sharp object had pierced his temple, twisting it in the process!

Ouch… In his stupor, Zhou Mingrui tried to turn over, hold his head, and sit up, but he couldn’t move his limbs. They refused to budge, leaving him completely immobilized and helpless.

It looks like I’m still not awake, still dreaming… Maybe in a short while I’ll think I’m awake, but I’m still sleeping… Zhou Mingrui, used to such disorienting experiences, struggled to focus and break free from the shackles of darkness and confusion.

However, while half-awake, he tried to focus his will that felt as insubstantial as a wisp of fog—there one moment and gone the next. His thoughts refused to be controlled or examined. No matter how hard he tried, his focus kept slipping away as random notions and images bubbled up unbidden.

Why would I suddenly get such a terrible headache in the middle of the night?

And it’s so painful!

Could it be a cerebral hemorrhage or something?

F**k, am I going to die young like this?

I need to wake up! Now!

Huh? It doesn’t hurt as much as before, but it still feels like a blunt knife is slowly slicing through my brain…

Looks like I can’t go back to sleep. How am I supposed to work tomorrow?

Why am I even thinking about work? With a headache like this, I should take the day off! No need to worry about the manager’s nagging!

Hey, putting it that way, it doesn’t seem too bad. Hehe, I can end up getting some spare time for myself!

The throbbing pain allowed Zhou Mingrui to gradually gather immaterial strength. Finally, he straightened his back and opened his eyes, fully breaking free from his reverie.

His vision first blurred, then was tinged with a faint crimson. He saw a wooden desk in front of him with an open notebook in the center. The pages were coarse and yellowed, with an eye-catching sentence written in deep black ink at the top.

To the left of the notebook was a stack of neatly arranged books, numbering about eight. The wall to their right had grayish-white pipes and a wall lamp connected to them.

The lamp had a classic Western style, about half the size of an adult’s head, with a transparent glass inner layer and a black metal grid on the outside.

Diagonally beneath the extinguished wall lamp was a black ink bottle bathed in a pale red glow. Its embossed surface formed a blurry angel pattern.

In front of the ink bottle, to the right of the notebook, lay a dark-colored pen with a rounded body. Its tip shimmered faintly, and its cap rested next to a brass revolver.

A gun? A revolver? Zhou Mingrui was stunned. Everything he saw was so unfamiliar and looked nothing like his room!

In his shock and confusion, he noticed that the desk, notebook, ink bottle, and revolver were covered in a layer of crimson “veil” from the light shining through the window.

Subconsciously, he lifted his head and his gaze slowly moved upwards.

In midair, against a backdrop of ‘black velvet curtains,’ a crimson moon hung high, shining silently.

Wh— Zhou Mingrui felt inexplicably terrified and stood up abruptly. But before he could straighten his legs, his head throbbed with pain again, causing him to lose strength and fall back heavily onto the hard wooden chair.

Thud!

The pain did little. Zhou Mingrui propped himself up with his hands on the table, stood up again, and turned around in a panic, examining his surroundings.

It was a small room with a brown door on each side and a wooden bunk bed against the opposite wall.

Between the bed and the left door was a cabinet with two open doors on top and five drawers below.

Next to the cabinet, at about the height of a person, was another grayish-white pipe connected to a strange mechanical device with some exposed gears and bearings.

In the right corner of the room near the desk were items resembling coal stoves, along with soup pots, iron pots, and other kitchen utensils.

Across from the right door was a dressing mirror with two cracks. Its wooden base had simple and plain patterns.

With a quick glance, Zhou Mingrui caught a glimpse of himself in the mirror—the current him: black hair, brown eyes, a linen shirt, a thin build, average features, but with a rather deep outline…

Wh— Zhou Mingrui gasped, his mind flooded with helpless and confused thoughts.

The revolver, the classical Western decor, and the crimson moon different from Earth’s moon all indicated one thing!

C-Could I have transmigrated? Zhou Mingrui’s mouth slowly opened.

He had grown up reading web novels and often fantasized about such scenarios. But when it really happened, he found it hard to accept.

Almost a minute later, Zhou Mingrui muttered to himself, trying to find some humor in his situation, This is probably what it means to love a fantasy[1]?

If it weren’t for the persistent headache keeping his thoughts sharp, he would have definitely thought he was dreaming.

Calm down, calm down, calm down… After taking a few deep breaths, Zhou Mingrui tried hard to stop panicking.

At that moment, as his mind and body calmed down, memories began flooding him, slowly appearing in his mind!

Klein Moretti, a citizen of the Northern Continent’s Loen Kingdom, Awashire, City of Tingen. He is also a recent graduate from the Department of History at Khoy University…

His father was a sergeant in the Imperial Army who died in a colonial conflict on the Southern Continent. The compensation money allowed Klein to attend a private grammar school, laying the foundation for his university admission…

His mother was a devotee of the Evernight Goddess. She passed away the year Klein passed the entrance examinations to Khoy University…

He also has an elder brother and a younger sister. They live together in a two bedroom apartment…

Their family is not wealthy, even struggling. They are currently supported by his elder brother who works as a clerk at an import and export company…

As a history graduate, Klein had learned the ancient Feysac language—considered the source of all languages in the Northern Continent—and the Hermes language often found in ancient mausoleums related to rituals and prayers…

Hermes language? Zhou Mingrui’s mind stirred. He reached out to rub his throbbing temples and looked at the open notebook on the desk. The text on the yellowed paper went from strange to alien, then from alien to familiar, until it became readable.

It was text written in Hermes language!

The dark ink said: “Everyone will die, including me.”

Hiss! Zhou Mingrui felt inexplicably horrified. He instinctively leaned back, trying to distance himself from the notebook and the text on it.

He was so weak he nearly fell, but managed to grab the edge of the table in a panic. The surrounding air felt turbulent, with faint whispers echoing around him. It reminded him of hearing horror stories from his elders when he was young.

He shook his head, telling himself it was just an illusion. Zhou Mingrui steadied himself, shifted his gaze from the notebook, and took deep breaths.

This time, his gaze landed on the shimmering brass revolver. A sudden question popped into his mind.

With Klein’s family situation, how could they afford or even get a revolver? Zhou Mingrui couldn’t help but frown.

While deep in thought, he suddenly noticed a red handprint on the edge of the table. Its color was deeper than the moonlight and thicker than the ‘veil.’

It was a bloody handprint!

A bloody handprint? Zhou Mingrui subconsciously turned over his right hand that had been holding the edge of the table. Looking down, he saw his palm and fingers were covered in blood.

At the same time, the throbbing pain in his head continued. Although it had weakened a little, it was still persistent.

Did I smash my head? Zhou Mingrui wondered as he turned around and walked towards the cracked dressing mirror.

A few steps later, a medium-built figure with black hair and brown eyes came into view. The person had a distinctly scholarly air.

Is this me now? Klein Moretti?

Zhou Mingrui paused for a moment. Due to the dim light, he couldn’t see clearly, so he moved forward until he was just a step away from the mirror.

Using the crimson moonlight, he turned his head to check the side of his forehead.

The clear reflection in the mirror showed a grotesque wound on his temple, with burn marks around it. The area was stained with blood, and grayish-white brain matter slowly wriggled within.

Chapter 50:
Old Neil’s Method of Repayment

Half past seven in the evening, around the Moretti family’s dining table.

“Klein, why do you need to be at work so early as a consultant? Would emergency matters at the security company be more dangerous?” Benson forked a potato from a dish of potato-stewed beef as he raised the matter in concern.

Klein carefully spat out the bones from a pan-fried fish and gave his prepared answer.

“A batch of historical documents needed immediate shipping to Backlund. I had to be present to handle the handover and make sure there was nothing missing. As you can guess, the bunch of fist-swinging bastards don’t know any Feysac.”

Upon hearing his answer, Benson, who had finished chewing his food, could not help but sigh.

“Knowledge is truly important.”

Making use of this opportunity, Klein took out the remaining five-pound note and handed it to Benson.

“This is my additional payment I received today. It’s time you get some decent clothes too.”

“Five pounds?” Benson and Melissa said in unison.

Benson took the note and looked at it repeatedly. He said in both shock and doubt, “This security company sure is generous…”

His weekly salary was one pound ten soli, which meant six pounds exactly every four weeks. He only earned one additional pound from this additional payment!

And with that salary, he had managed to support his siblings, giving them a decent place to stay and allowing them to eat meat two to three times a week. Every year, they could get a few new clothes!

“Are you doubting me?” Klein deliberately returned with a question.

Benson chuckled. “I doubt you have the ability nor the guts to rob a bank.”

“You aren’t someone who can lie,” Melissa answered seriously after lowering her fork and knife.

I-I’m now someone used to lying… Klein immediately felt a little ashamed.

Although it was a result of the circumstances of his reality, his sister’s belief in him left him melancholic.

“It was relatively urgent and important today. I also played a crucial role… which is the reason for the five pounds,” Klein explained.

In a way, what he said was the truth.

As for the five pounds he was to be reimbursed—the very sum he planned to use to join the Divination Club—he intended to keep it hidden. First, if he brought home another five pounds, he would truly alarm his siblings, who might suspect him of doing something illegal. Second, he needed to save up for extra materials to practice Seership and deepen his knowledge of mysticism.

Benson bit off a mouthful of oat bread in satisfaction and thought for more than ten seconds.

“The work I’m at doesn’t need any decent clothes. Well, to be precise, the clothes at home are sufficient.”

Without waiting for Klein to persuade him, he suggested, “With this additional income, we would truly have savings. I plan on buying a few books on accountancy and studying. Klein, Melissa, I do not wish that my weekly salary remains below two pounds in five years. Heh, as you know, my boss and manager have shit for brains. Their mouths stink the moment they open them.”

“Excellent idea,” agreed Klein. He also took the opportunity to steer the conversation. “Why don’t you read some of the grammar books in my room? To be truly dignified and to earn a handsome pay, that’s something rather critical.”

Perhaps, in the times to come, the civil servant examinations will appear in the Loen Kingdom. Preparing ahead of time would give him the advantage…

Benson’s eyes lit up when he heard that.

“I’ve indeed forgotten about that. Here, let’s toast to a beautiful future.”

He did not drink rye beer. Instead, he poured clear oyster soup into three cups and clinked his cup with his siblings’.

After drinking the clear soup, he looked at his sister who was wrestling with the pan-fried fish. He chuckled and said, “Aside from Benson’s books, I think Melissa needs a new dress too.”

Melissa looked up and shook her head incessantly.

“No, I think it’s best…”

“To save it up.” Klein finished the sentence for her.

“Yeah.” Melissa nodded in agreement.

“In fact, if you do not seek the best fabrics and the newest designs, it would not be too expensive. We can save up the remaining money,” said Klein in a manner which did not allow for disagreement.

Benson added, “Melissa, are you planning on wearing the old dress again to Selena’s sixteenth birthday bash?”

Selena Wood was Melissa’s classmate and good friend. She came from quite a good family background. Her elder brother was a practicing solicitor and her father was a senior employee of Backlund Bank’s Tingen branch.

However, the so-called bash was only a dinner invitation to friends where they chatted and played cards.

“Alright.” Melissa lowered her head and mumbled a response. Then, she ruthlessly forked a piece of stewed beef.

After a short silence, she suddenly recalled something and looked up abruptly.

“Mrs. Shaud from next door got her maidservant to send a calling card over. She wishes to make a formal visit on Sunday, at four in the afternoon tomorrow. She wants to get to know her new neighbors.”

“Mrs. Shaud?” Klein looked at his siblings, confounded.

Benson rapped the side of the table with his fingers and appeared to be thinking.

“Mrs. Shaud from 4 Daffodil Street? I met her husband before. He’s a senior solicitor.”

“Senior solicitor… Perhaps he knows Selena’s brother,” said Melissa with some hints of delight.

We are at 2 Daffodil Street… Klein nodded slightly.

“It’s imperative we get to know our neighbors, but as you know, I still have to be at the company on Sunday. I only have time off on Monday. Please pass my apologies to Mrs. Shaud.”

With that said, he suddenly recalled the neighbors of his former life when he was young, as well as the neighbors in the apartment from Ironcross Street. He was amused as he sighed lightly.

“To have formal visits… Shouldn’t neighbors get to know each other through natural interaction?”

“Haha, Klein, that’s because you don’t know. You’ve been reading plenty of newspapers lately, but not the magazines aimed at families and middle-aged women. They classify households with an annual income of a hundred to a thousand pounds as middle class. They promote this group as the backbone of the entire kingdom, praising how the middle class lacks the arrogance of the aristocrats and the wealthy, yet isn’t as crude as the lower-income brackets.”

Benson explained lightly and cheerfully, “These magazines also introduce simplified versions of aristocratic etiquette for social interactions. That’s why the middle class adopts them, leading to distinctions between intimate calls, semi-formal calls, and formal calls.”

As he spoke, he shook his head and chuckled.

“Typically, gentlemen, madams, and ladies who view themselves in this class will be very particular about details. They will visit their neighbors and friends from two to six in the afternoon. It’s known as a morning call[12].”

“Morning call?” Klein and Melissa asked in surprise.

Why was a visit from two to six in the afternoon a morning call?

Benson put down his fork and knife, threw his hands up, and smiled.

“I do not know why either. All I did was read the magazines my female colleague brought. Yeah, perhaps it’s because they wear their morning gowns to make the call…”

Morning gowns were a form of formal attire worn during Mass or gatherings. Later, it was considered as formal attire for the day, different from the formal attire for evening functions.

“Alright. Remember to buy some good coffee powder and tea leaves in the afternoon. Buy some muffins and lemon egg tarts from Mrs. Smyrin. We must not ill-treat our neighbors.” Klein chuckled as he dipped his remaining bread into the meat sauces, grabbed some potato and put it into his mouth.

†

The next morning was a Sunday morning.

Klein finished the last mouthful of inferior tea, put down the newspapers, and wore his halved top hat. Picking up his silver-inlaid black cane, he sauntered out the door and took a public carriage to Zouteland Street.

He greeted Rozanne who was planning to sleep in the break room after finishing her night duty. After which, he went all the way down to the basement.

After turning a corner, he met a Nighthawk member, Sleepless Royale Reideen.

She looked like a cold lady. Her brows were long and slender, sitting atop large eyes. Her hair was a silky-smooth black.

“Good morning, Madam Reideen,” Klein greeted with a smile.

Royale used her deep blue eyes to glance at him and nodded indiscernibly in return.

The two quickly passed by each other when Royale stopped and said with her eyes trained forward, “Ritualistic magic is a very dangerous thing.”

Ah… Klein was taken aback. By the time he turned around, all he saw was her departing back.

“Thank you.” He frowned and shouted at Royale Reideen’s back.

After taking a left bend, he quickly met Old Neil inside the armory, as well as Bredt who should not have been there.

“Let’s go to my place. I’ve already received the corresponding materials. Bredt has agreed to watch the armory for me,” said Old Neil with a chuckle.

Klein was immediately surprised.

“We aren’t doing it here?”

Old Neil held a silver chest and tutted.

“There’s no space here to practice ritualistic magic.”

Klein did not ask further. He followed Old Neil up to the streets and took a public carriage to the North Borough’s suburbs.

Old Neil’s place was a bungalow. The garden in front of it was filled with roses, gold mint, and other “materials.”

The moment he entered, there was a carpeted foyer. There were two high-back chairs and an umbrella rack.

Through the foyer was an expansive living room. The walls were plastered with light-colored wallpaper. The floors were a dark brown color. In the middle of the room was a tiny carpet with floral imprints and placed above it was a heavy round table.

Surrounding the table were comfortable long benches, single-seaters, and a piano.

“My deceased wife loved music.” Old Neil pointed at the piano and mentioned in passing, “The sofa and coffee table are in the bedrooms… Let’s do the ritualistic magic in the living room.”

“Alright,” Klein replied cautiously.

After Old Neil put down the silver chest, he laughed and said, “Let me demonstrate to you ritualistic magic. Make sure to observe and remember the ritual.”

As he spoke, he took out a fake goatskin parchment from the chest. It was specially made and it had strange pictures drawn on it with black ink that exuded a serene fragrance.

Klein kept watching and finally discovered that Old Neil was seemingly, likely, possibly drawing an IOU!

When Old Neil filled in the corresponding field with the number “30” and the corresponding “£” symbol, Klein could not help but ask out of puzzlement and confusion, “Mr. Neil, what kind of ritualistic magic are you doing?”

Old Neil coughed and answered very seriously, “I’ll be using magic to settle that debt of thirty pounds today.”

You can do that? Klein’s eyes widened as his mouth gaped.

Chapter 53:
Listener

An ancient three-masted sailboat was navigating through a tumultuous storm in the sea.

It was not fast and its displacement was lacking. With the weather and the sea looking like a cataclysmic scene, the sailboat was like a withered leaf separated from its tree. However, regardless of how the typhoons rampaged or how terrifying the waves were, it continued sailing peacefully without any signs of tilting.

Alger Wilson stood on the empty deck as he looked at the massive waves that resembled mountains. His thoughts were a mystery.

It’s going to be Monday again… he muttered silently to himself.

It was the day belonging to Earth Mother, the beginning of a series of waxing and waning.

However, it meant something different to Alger. It belonged to a mysterious existence forever enveloped in grayish-white fog.

At least I haven’t been reduced to a madman… He stopped looking around as he gave a self-deprecating chuckle.

At this moment, one of the only few sailors he had leaned over and asked reverently, “My Lord, where are we setting course for this time?”

Alger surveyed his surroundings and said in a calm voice, “Pursue the Listener from the Aurora Order.”

†

The storm subsided as mist emanated. On a strange sailboat with cannons on board, an eight or nine-year-old boy with soft yellow hair was looking at pirates around him in fear. They were disorderly—some enjoyed barrels of beer, some swung around with ropes, others mocked each other, and some even fought with their fists.

He turned to look at a black-robed man standing in the shadows. He suppressed his voice and asked, “Father, where are we going?”

Five days ago was his first time seeing his father, a father who proclaimed to be an adventurer.

If not for the oil painting his late mother left him that confirmed his father’s identity and the fact that the orphanage had opened its doors to him, he was absolutely unwilling to leave his hometown and follow his only kin who was also nearly a stranger.

The man in the shadows lowered his head and looked at his son. With an amiable expression, he answered, “Jack, I’m bringing you to a holy place, a holy residence where the Creator once lived.”

“Is that the Kingdom of God? We mortals can only enter by winning His grace…” Jack had been well-educated by his mother and knew this much. He was both surprised and fearful about the matter.

Standing in the shadows, the man had an unforgettable jawline as though he was a sculpture chiseled by the best artisan.

He placed his hand to his ear and made a listening pose. He replied in a tone that sounded like sleep-talking, “Jack, mortals are a wrong concept. The Creator created this world and He is everywhere. He exists in every living being. Therefore, all beings have godhood. Once the godhood attains a particular level, they can become an angel. The seven fake gods at present are only powerful angels.

“Look, I can now hear the teachings of the Creator. Ah, how extraordinary is this revelation! Life is only a tour of the spirit. When the spirit is sufficiently potent and resilient, we can find our godhood and fuse with even more godhoods…”

Jack could not understand the complicated description. He shook his head and asked another question he previously did not have the chance to.

“Father, I heard from Mother that after the Creator created this world, He split into all beings and does not exist in actuality. Then, why does His holy residence exist?”

As a seven to eight-year-old child, he was logical.

The man with the chiseled face was taken aback. He turned his head away as though he was listening to more murmurings.

Suddenly, he slumped down, knees on the deck. His exposed skin protruded black shards.

He clenched his head with both hands as his expression warped and he shouted in extreme pain, “They are lying!”

†

After lunch, having had Old Neil promise him that he would bring him to the underground market the next time he went, Klein slowly returned to the Blackthorn Security Company. He chose the two options of reading the documents in the staff office and practicing his abilities or take the opportunity to go out and act as a Seer in the Divination Club before Captain Dunn stopped him.

However, before he could make the decision, he saw Dunn Smith walk in. He was dressed in the usual black trench coat and halved top hat.

“Captain, any updates?” Klein thought of the whereabouts of the Antigonus family’s notebook as he asked with concern.

Without showing any signs of fatigue in his gray eyes, Dunn said, “The facts have corroborated that the Antigonus family’s notebook is in Ray Bieber’s hands. However, he has vanished completely.

“I have already informed the various Nighthawks teams of this matter through a telegram. They were requested to pay attention to the various piers and steam locomotive stations. The first batch of printed portraits was mailed out yesterday afternoon and will be printed in various major newspapers.”

How nice it would be if there were phones, fax machines, surveillance cameras, and big data… What a pity. I know how to use all of them and even understand a little of the logic behind it… Klein exhaled silently.

“But regardless, we can consider ourselves as having found the notebook. And this is all thanks to you. Of course, it still needs another round of confirmations. I have already sent a telegram to the Backlund diocese, requesting them to escort Sealed Artifact 2-049 here. It was once a dangerous item of the Antigonus family. It can help us know if Ray Bieber is a descendant of the Antigonus family.”

A Grade 2 Sealed Artifact… Dangerous… They can be used with care and moderation. Klein had originally wanted to ask about the Sealed Artifact, its special abilities, and the danger it posed out of curiosity, but he instantly recalled that he lacked the necessary clearance. He had no choice but to give up.

“May Goddess bless us.” Klein tapped four spots on his chest, forming the sign of the full moon.

Dunn pushed open the door to his office and, with a slight nod, said, “The Goddess has always been watching over us. Klein, if you hadn’t chosen Seer, you would already be a formal member once this matter is confirmed. You could have chosen Sleepless, but… pity. To be honest, I’m still puzzled by your decision. Corpse Collector is admittedly unpleasant, but you’ve seen Daly—you know Spirit Mediums can be formidable. And Mystery Pryers are a solid choice as well. At the very least, you’d have Old Neil as a guide, someone who can help minimize the risk of losing control.”

Klein had long prepared an answer to this question, though he had never had the chance to use it until now.

He paused to gather his thoughts, then replied, “My reasoning is that Seers and Mystery Pryers are both support-type Beyonders. They don’t always need to face enemies directly—that’s far too dangerous. And both you and Old Neil said that, in the realm of the Beyonders, curiosity and reckless experimentation often lead to terrifying consequences. Since Mystery Pryers are literally about ‘prying into mysteries,’ I became worried. Heh… as you know, I was just an ordinary university graduate not long ago. Honestly, my lack of courage is the only reason I made this choice.”

Dunn rubbed his temples and chuckled. “I have to say, that’s a very reasonable answer—better than I expected.”

He turned halfway as his gray eyes sized up Klein.

“Continue going out for now. Do not limit yourself to the paths leading from Welch’s place to Ironcross Street. Perhaps you might sense the notebook and help us confirm Ray Bieber’s location.”

“Alright.” Klein realized that he no longer needed to be in a dilemma.

He bade Dunn farewell and turned around, his heart beginning to count.

Three, two…

“Hold on,” shouted Dunn.

Klein turned his head and smiled.

“Captain, is there anything else?”

Dunn coughed slightly and said, “Well, support Beyonders have to fight their enemies from time to time. Although Seers sound like they can avoid such battles, they are not to be ignored. You have to maintain your shooting skills and work on increasing your strength.”

“This is what I’m working hard towards.” Klein pointed outside. “I’ll be leaving.”

“Alright. Uh, wait a moment.” Dunn shouted for him once more. As he pondered, he said, “Perhaps I have to consider hiring a combat trainer for you. Of course, this matter is under the premise that you become a formal member.”

Klein responded tersely before asking carefully, “Captain, is there anything else?”

“No.” Seeing Klein’s unbelieving eyes, Dunn shook his head and smiled. He emphasized again, “Really, nothing.”

Only then did Klein walk past the partition divider. He bade farewell to Rozanne and Mrs. Orianna and headed to the Shooting Club for practice.

With all of this done, he went to the Divination Club and saw the beautiful Angelica sitting there reading magazines leisurely.

“Home”… Klein silently read. With the cane in hand, he walked over and greeted with a smile, “Good afternoon, Madam Angelica.”

“Good afternoon, Mr. Moretti.” In no rush, Angelica put down her magazine. She stood up and said, “Not long after you left yesterday, Mr. Glacis came. He just recovered from a major illness.”

Klein heaved a sigh of relief as he smiled.

“That sure is something worth celebrating.”

Upon hearing this, Angelica, who was secretly observing him, lowered her voice and asked out of curiosity, “Mr. Glacis said that you are a very, very, very magical doctor. Are you?”

What? Klein froze, staring at the lady before him, wondering if he had heard her correctly.

What made him think I’m a doctor?

Even I’m unaware…

Chapter 57:
Organization and Summary

After pausing for a moment, Klein continued writing.

“The key to resolving problems with potions lies in digestion, not mere control. This is fairly straightforward to understand.

“Simply controlling a potion is like treating its power as an external tool. A tamed beast, no matter how obedient, never truly becomes part of you. The risk of it turning against you always remains. Digestion, on the other hand, is about making the potion a part of yourself. You break it down, fuse with it, absorb it, and integrate it into a unified system.

“I am confident of this point. What matters even more is how ‘acting’ facilitates digestion.

“From my experience as a Seer today, I can propose two hypotheses, which can be tested in the future.

“First: Acting in accordance with the potion’s name alters the state of one’s body, heart, and soul, aligning them with the residual, headstrong psyche of the potion’s core. This resonance allows gradual assimilation and absorption.

“Second: The residual headstrong psyche of the potion may function like a computer with complete defensive mechanisms. Attempting to attack and break it down directly is futile—you must find a bug, a security flaw, or a key. The potion’s name offers a clue. By acting in harmony with it, one can disguise the body, heart, and soul as ‘part of the system,’ thereby bypassing its defenses. This approach mirrors Emperor Roselle’s descriptions.

“Regardless of which hypothesis proves correct, the body, heart, and soul remain essential—they are the only bridge between acting and the true power of potions.”

Klein put down his pen and looked at the paragraph of text. For a moment, he even wanted to thank the education he received from the Foodaholic Empire.

Regardless of whether he had chosen science or engineering for further study, he possessed the fundamentals of logical thinking. Otherwise, he couldn’t have become a keyboard warrior, nor would he be able to analyze his current situation.

“Acting might have an effect, but we’ll have to wait and see for the specifics,” Klein guessed.

After that, he wrote down his second question.

“Why would a Seer, being more well-learned and professional in the domain of mysticism, be lacking in means when it comes to direct combat? Wouldn’t being more well-learned and professional make a Seer even more powerful, giving them the ability to discover a way to defeat their enemies?

“The reasons could be…

“First, just like the web novels I’ve read in the past, I have transmigrated to a game world that has become reality. Thus, different ‘jobs’ come with different specialties that have to be balanced against each other. But up to this point, there has been no sign of this world being a game, nor are there signs of mission-like developments. I’ll put this reason on hold, but it’s very unlikely.

“Second, the fundamental law of this world is balance. The Creator made this world with the core idea of balance.

“Third, potions at the same Sequence level would have the same level of power. It is the most optimal state based on what our forefathers found out and summarized. Exceeding this level of power would make it easier for one to collapse and lose control. Below this level of power would make it such that one would not obtain the desired Beyonder powers. Thus, under the situation of a balanced power level, being stronger in one area would naturally mean that one is weaker in another area.

“Fourth, everything in this world originated from the same source; they were formed by the remnants of the Creator. Thus, everything in this world is technically fragments of the Creator, and the fact that they have to complement each other would mean that there are inherent shortcomings to an individual.

“I am leaning towards the third and fourth reasons, but the latter stems from an unconfirmed myth and can only serve as a guide.

“Thus, I shall use the third reason as a guide, and try to ascertain it using my current knowledge and future studies.”

At this point, Klein had already written two full pages but did not stop. Instead, he penned a new question.

“From what I learned today, my luck enhancement ritual is categorized as classic ritualistic magic.

“Similar kinds of ritualistic magic can be split into three parts, the first being a sacrifice that sparks the interest of a corresponding existence. The second consists of incantations specifically describing the existence in question. The third is using simple formatting and symbols to convey what one is asking for.

“Using this as a benchmark to analyze the luck enhancement ritual, there’s an obvious problem. “There is no third part!

“It has the sacrifice aspect in the placement of staple foods and walking a square in a counterclockwise manner with four steps. There is also a clear indication who the incantation is for, such as the phrase, ‘The Immortal Lord of Heaven and Earth for Blessings.’

“But all I did after was close my eyes and wait. There was nothing in the ritual that described the goal of enhancing my luck.

“In other words, the corresponding existence has no way of knowing what the so-called luck enhancement ritual is asking for, and can only do as they see fit… Do as they see fit…

“What a troll! Isn’t that darn ‘Quintessential Divination and Arcane Arts of the Qin and Han Dynasty’ too much of a troll?

“I must have had rocks in my head back then for trying…”

Klein stopped writing and took two deep breaths, trying hard to calm himself down.

He spat out a foul breath and continued writing.

“I can consider re-designing the ritual, making it more complete. The motive of the ritual shall be to return to Earth, back to the world with my parents and friends.

“Then here comes the question: was the entity truly acting on a whim? Or is there a deeper meaning to it?

“Also, is the entity that the descriptive incantations point towards in this world the same one from Earth?

“If so, the difference in results between the first and second ritual could be explained as the entity doing as it wishes. But the results of me appearing above the gray fog during the second and third time, while being able to connect to Justice and The Hanged Man has basically no differences. Why would that be so?

“If the fourth ritual tomorrow afternoon shows me the same stable results, that would mean that the effects are consistent. That would mean that the unknown entity has an agenda I do not know about. If that is the case, adding new descriptions and requests would not get me a clear response. In fact, it might complicate the ritual and result in adverse effects.

“Would the difference between the first ritual and the subsequent rituals—under the premise that the entity I called upon is the same one—mean that the results would be different depending on the world I’m in? It is like I am using a different interface…

“Then how can I design it to obtain my desired outcome?

“If I think that the entities behind the first and subsequent rituals are different, some of the questions can be perfectly answered. But similarly, the stability of the results in the second and third rituals would mean that the entity I am praying to has a certain agenda, and there is no way I can change that for the time being.

“The most important question is the identity of the entity that the ritual is directed. Where is He, and why doesn’t He give me any clues or guidance?

“Could He be deep in the world of fog?

“Hmm, can I treat Him as an entity in slumber, an entity that would give fixed responses if I give Him a certain stimulus, but would not interfere with what I do other than that?

“Then I can introduce a different ritual as a stimulus and conclude whether the feedback I receive is regular. That way, I can find the correct method of returning.

“But the problem lies in the possibility that He is not asleep. In that case, such tests might result in terrifying outcomes. It might be really dangerous.

“The first attempt must be conducted with extreme caution. The design must not anger the being…

“What a headache. I need more knowledge.”

Klein sighed and gave a summary.

Finally, he wrote down other miscellaneous items.

“There are always formless voices resonating in my ears, shouting ‘Hornacis and… uh, was it saying Frygrea or Feygrea?

“Hornacis is the mountain range dividing the Loen Kingdom and the Intis Republic. Its main peak is six thousand meters above sea level.

“According to the records in the Antigonus family’s diary, there existed a Nation of the Evernight in the Fourth Epoch. Is the Nation of the Evernight related to the Evernight Goddess—is there any connection between the two? Are they allies or enemies? Was the Antigonus family obliterated by the Church of Evernight due to Nation of the Evernight?

“Did I hear murmurings coming from the diary, from the howls of the Antigonus family over one or two thousand years?

“What then does Frygrea, uh—Flegrea mean?

“An interesting question. To be able to leave behind such a diary, to leave behind Sealed Artifact 2-049 implies that the Antigonus family had possession of a relatively powerful Beyonder power. If that is so, which Sequence did they possess? Was it complete or not complete?

“My realization that the diary is in the hands of Ray Bieber was a bit of a coincidence, but without any indication of it being arranged, could my fate really be tied up with that diary’s?”

†

His ideas were penned on the pieces of paper. Klein tried his best to write down the events he had experienced and his guesses about their meaning.

He wrote a total of four pages on both sides of each paper.

Rip! Klein suddenly tore off the four pages and read them from top to bottom, sometimes marking certain sections with his pen, adding a few sentences at other times.

Time flew quickly. The crimson moon was temporarily covered by dark clouds. Klein picked up the pocket watch on the table, snapped it open, and looked at the time.

He put down the watch and took out a box of matches from his drawer. He lit one and brought it close to the four pages of notes.

The orange flame ignited the edges of the paper and quickly spread.

Klein placed the notes on top of the wooden dustbin and watched the ashes drop.

He then released his fingers, allowing the papers to fall. In just ten seconds, everything had disappeared. All that was left was the still-swirling ash and the charred bottom of the dustbin.

As there was Emperor Roselle’s secret diary in this world, Klein did not dare leave behind any evidence that he knew how to write Chinese—if Old Neil and the rest discovered the four pieces of paper he wrote, he would have no idea how to explain the matter.

And while writing the confidential questions, Klein was worried that the one paying attention to his dreams would be able to see and decipher the contents no matter which language he used, be it Loen, ancient Feysac, or Hermes. Therefore, he could only write notes in Chinese to organize and summarize. After he was done with the task, he burned the notes to leave no traces.

And precisely because there was no way of saving, he set up a plan for himself. He would do this summary once a week just in case he forgot anything.

As he watched the ashes fall, Klein pulled out a white piece of paper. He wrote the title: “To my respected mentor,”

He wanted to write to Senior Associate Professor Quentin Cohen, asking if he had any relevant historical information about the main peak of the Hornacis mountain range.

Chapter 58:
A Train of Thought

The next day, a Monday morning.

Klein, who had the day off, didn’t leave home. Instead, he gave Melissa his letter directed to Mentor Cohen Quentin and more than enough money to buy stamps. He entrusted her with the job of mailing the letter at the post office near the Tingen Technical School where she studied.

After breakfast, he slept in to make up for the lack of sleep caused by the previous night’s “work.” He only woke up because of his stomach’s grumblings close to noon.

He heated up some leftovers from the night before and ate them with a loaf of rye bread. Klein grabbed a newspaper and entered the bathroom on the second floor.

Whenever he did that, he couldn’t help but sigh at the lack of a cell phone.

After about seven or eight minutes, he left the toilet refreshed and washed his hands. He then returned to his bedroom and locked his door.

Klein drew the curtains, lit up the gas lamp, and cogitated for half an hour. After practicing his Spiritual Vision, spirit dowsing, and dowsing rod for half an hour, he spent another hour mentally reviewing the mysticism knowledge he had gained recently.

After that, he tore up the old newspaper and crumpled the pieces into a few balls. On them, he wrote the names of ingredients: “Moon Flower Candle,” “Full Moon Essence Oil,” and others. In his mind, he went through the prescribed steps of ritualistic magic, striving to master every detail. He had no intention of attempting the ritual for real until he knew it inside out—both because using the materials prematurely would be wasteful and because it was far too dangerous.

He repeated again and again until he picked up his silver pocket watch patterned with vine-leaves and took a glance. He realized that it was a quarter to three.

He considered for a few seconds and brought the scraps of old newspapers to the kitchen on the first floor to burn them. While doing so, he made sure he was in an optimal state of mind as he prepared for the Tarot Gathering.

Locking his bedroom door once again, Klein didn’t wait for the clock to strike three. He planned to enter the area above the gray fog ahead of time.

He wanted to seize the chance to explore the place thoroughly!

As Klein stood in an empty spot in his room and started walking counterclockwise, he suddenly worried that Justice and The Hanged Man had yet to enter a suitable environment. He thought of a particular matter.

Would they be disturbed or discovered?

He had previously mentioned to allow Justice and The Hanged Man to apply for “leave” ahead of time if they needed to be absent from the Gathering for some reason such as being unable to find time alone or unexpected circumstances.

It would have been an almost unsolvable problem for Klein in the past. There was no way he could build an entire server-based Internet by hand in a different world, right? Any technology beyond the telegram could expose him.

But now, he had suddenly found inspiration from ritualistic magic.

“Ritualistic magic borrows the powers of others by seeking the help of different existences. Similar incantations would make it clear who it is directed to in the beginning, such as the Evernight Goddess or the Lady of Crimson. It would be a description of the unknown and clandestine existences.”

“Then, can I amend the chant and redirect the beginning of the chant towards myself?”

“Directed at me…”

“This way, even if Justice and The Hanged Man perform the ritual in different locations, I would still receive their messages.”

Klein suddenly felt a surge of insight as he began calculating the likelihood of the method working.

“There are two problems. First, I’m not an exceptionally powerful High-Sequence Beyonder. Even if the incantation were specifically directed at me, I couldn’t possibly receive the ‘request.’”

“Second, how can I ensure that the description of the chant is directed at me accurately, and doesn’t stray away and hit some other unknown existence that fits the description? That would be incredibly dangerous.”

Klein paced back and forth, deep in thought for a possible workable solution.

He went in circles with silent footsteps. Then, he naturally linked the matter with the mysterious world of the gray fog.

“Even if I can’t receive the message myself, that doesn’t mean the gray fog can’t. Its connection to the crimson stars can ‘pull’ a person into the space directly, no matter where they are in the physical world.

“I could consider linking myself to the mysterious space at the same time as the directed incantation…

“Following this line of thought, even if I don’t immediately receive the ‘request’ while the other party performs the ritual, I would still be able to see the corresponding messages whenever I enter the gray fog.

“In other words, it’s like the difference between being online and offline on an instant messaging system.”

Klein became more excited the more he thought. He felt that his idea was worth a try.

“Hmm… what kind of incantation could precisely direct a message to both me and the gray fog world?” He began considering the practical details.

In truth, there was an incantation that would definitely work: the Loen translation of The Celestial Worthy of Heaven and Earth for Blessings. But the problem was clear—using it would mean losing control of the gray fog and forfeiting his leading role. He had no choice but to discard it.

“The Fool from an alternate world?” No—it is remarkably precise, and there is almost no other existence that fits the criteria, but using it would reveal my greatest secret… One by one, Klein considered various incantations, crossing each off the list.

After seven or eight minutes, he finally settled on the description for the first paragraph, the one directed at himself.

“The Fool that doesn’t belong to this era.”

It was obviously not accurate enough; therefore, Klein quickly added, “The mysterious ruler above the gray fog.”

The combination of the two lines practically limited it to him. Furthermore, he had tied the gray fog to him.

“It’s still a little short. I cannot eliminate the possibility that there are multiple spaces and rulers above the gray fog. I cannot eliminate the fact that the description might be directed to the spirit world…” Klein creased his eyebrows and planned on making it more certain.

Hmm… He thought for a full minute and finally decided on the last part of the description.

The King of Yellow and Black who wields good luck!

It shared a similar meaning to “The Exalted Thearch of Heaven and Earth[14] for Blessings.” If the incantation purely depended on that part of the description, it might end up being directed away and provoking unknown dangerous existences. But with the first two lines as a limitation, and his experience of arriving above the fog through a similar incantation, he believed that the target’s description could result in a perfect lock on.

Klein wasn’t sure if casting the ritualistic magic with those three descriptions would be effective, but he was definite that it would not attract the attention of another existence, It wouldn’t throw Justice and The Hanged Man into danger.

Klein heaved out a long sigh and recited the incantation that he had decided upon.

The Fool that doesn’t belong to this era, you are the mysterious ruler above the gray fog; you are the King of Yellow and Black who wields good luck…

He nodded slightly and took out his pocket watch to confirm the time.

It’s already 2:58… Without further thought, Klein put away his pocket and entered Cogitation. Soon he chanted and took four steps counterclockwise to form a square.

The most ferocious noises and heart-stirring roars were heard once again. He felt the headache that was even harder to deal with than the pain of consuming the Seer potion.

The pain was not a sharp pain that tore through his head. It was a throbbing pain that made him manic and irrational. It was a pain that left him in chaotic confusion.

Klein controlled himself using Cogitation and tried hard to ignore the voices.

The muttering and murmurs receded like the tides. His body became ethereal, along with his spirituality. Everything seemed to float.

The boundless gray fog appeared before his sight, the crimson stars at varying distances from him, just like pairs of eyes.

Above the gray fog stood the palace, lofty and towering like the home of a giant. It was as though it had been there for millions of years.

All Klein did was will it and he disappeared from where he was, reappearing at the Seat of Honor at the long bronze table with twenty-two high-back chairs.

“The effect of the ritual is definitely fixed…” Klein muttered. He tapped his glabella gently and allowed the fog to engulf him, ones thicker than before. According to the description of The Hanged Man, if Justice had become a Spectator, it would be best not to reveal any of his tics before her.

Without any time for exploring, Klein extended his right hand and formed an invisible connection, connecting him to the two familiar crimson stars.

†

On the roaring blue waves of the Sonia Sea, an ancient sailboat was sailing with the wind.

Alger Wilson locked himself in the captain’s cabin and made the ghost ship provide him the best protection.

He opened the pocket watch before him and laid it next to the brass sextant. The clock was ticking without joy as it exuded nervousness.

When the hour hand, minute hand, and second hand aligned, there was an explosion of crimson before Alger Wilson. It ignored the layers and layers of protection he had placed over himself.

Sigh… His sigh reverberated across the captain’s room.

†

Backlund, Empress Borough.

Audrey Hall laid against a down-feather pillow and glanced at the yellow paper in her hand. Her gemlike eyes looked like they had two souls spiraling slowly in them.

Her gaze was calm and cool, as if she were waiting for a play to begin.

As the crimson red erupted, she looked at herself being swallowed with complete detachment.

†

Above the gray fog, in the magnificent palace, on the ancient and mottled long bronze table.

Klein, who had already activated his Spiritual Vision, looked over when Audrey Hall’s figure began to form. He was not surprised to see that the colors deep in her aura had blended together. It became pure and serene, like a lake that was clear and reflective.

She really did become a Beyonder… Klein was just about to move his gaze away when he suddenly saw the chair belonging to Miss Justice change.

The bright stars on the back of the chair moved swiftly, forming an illusory constellation that didn’t belong to reality.

That constellation was familiar to Klein because it was one of the symbols of mysticism.

It was a symbol that represented “Giant Dragon”!

Spectator… Giant Dragon… Klein restrained himself from shaking his head and looked over at the back of The Hanged Man’s chair.

Typically speaking, it was impossible for him to see the back of the chair from his angle, but this was where he was in control. Everything presented itself according to his will.

The constellation on the back of the chair had not changed, but since Klein had grasped the basics of mysticism, he wasn’t as ignorant as before. He could recognize that it was the symbol of “Storm.”

Sailor… Keeper of the Sea… Storm… That’s reasonable. The color deep in The Hanged Man’s aura is much purer than it was… Has he advanced? Oh yeah, what about the symbol behind my chair?

Klein suppressed his impulse to look, rapped the edge of the long table thrice just like before, and smiled as he said, “Congratulations, Miss Justice, you are a Beyonder now.”

He can tell straight away? Audrey was stunned and smiled faintly.

“Thank you, Mr. Fool, and thank you, Mr. Hanged Man.”

“That was much faster that I thought,” Alger Wilson said honestly.

Klein didn’t continue the topic but tapped his glabella and said with a smile, “Lady, Sir, have either of you found Roselle’s diary?”

Chapter 63:
Dream Interpretation

Klein proceeded a few steps forward and saw the client. He was dressed in a formal black suit and a halved top hat. He held a gold-inlaid wooden cane and his short blond hair flared from the sides. His nose was aquiline like a hawk’s beak.

Anna’s fiancé… The Joyce Meyer that went through a terrifying ordeal. Klein, who had seen him in his dream divination, immediately greeted with a smile, “Good afternoon, Mr. Meyer.”

“Good afternoon, Mr. Moretti.” Joyce took off his hat and bowed in greeting. “Thank you for the advice you gave Anna. She cannot stop praising how miraculous you are.”

Klein chortled and said, “I did not change a thing. You should be thanking yourself. Without your determination and your hope for a better tomorrow, you wouldn’t have been able to overcome such an ordeal.”

After the exchange of pleasantries, Klein could not help but lampoon inwardly.

Does this count as mutual professional bootlicking?

“In all honesty, I still find my coming back alive a dream. I still cannot believe that I survived wave after wave of terrifying ordeals.” Joyce shook his head wistfully.

Without waiting for Klein’s reply, he asked curiously, “You knew who I was the moment you saw me. Was that because of my unique nose, or because you divined that I would visit you?”

“I had your detailed information. That is enough for a seer,” Klein answered vaguely, behaving like how a charlatan would.

Joyce was indeed stunned. More than ten seconds later, he squeezed a smile.

“Mr. Moretti, I wish to request a divination from you.”

The moment he finished his sentence, he suddenly realized something.

Mr. Klein Moretti had addressed himself as a seer, not a fortune-teller. A seer!

“Alright, let us head to Topaz.” Klein gestured.

At that moment, he felt as though he should have worn a long black robe. He tried to keep his words to a minimum to accentuate the mystique of a seer.

Joyce Meyer locked the door behind him after entering the divination room. While he observed his surroundings, Klein seized the opportunity to tap his glabella twice and activated his Spirit Vision.

Joyce sat down and set his cane down beside him. He pulled on his black bow tie and said hoarsely, “Mr. Moretti, I wish for you to interpret my dream.”

“Dream interpretation?” Klein acted as though it was within his expectations, but was merely asking for confirmation.

He saw that the colors representing Joyce’s health were dull, but none of them signified an impending illness. The colors symbolizing his emotions were predominantly blue, and its darkness showed that he was obviously high strung.

Joyce nodded seriously.

“I have had the same horrific dream every night ever since the Alfalfa arrived at Enmat Harbor. I know that this could be associated with the trauma of the ordeal and that I should go see a psychiatrist, but I suspect that this is no ordinary dream. A normal dream would definitely have some details that are different even if they recur every night, but this dream is, at the very least, constant in the parts which I can recall.”

“To a seer, these kinds of dreams are seen as revelations given by the divine,” Klein said, half consoling and half explaining. “Can you describe the dream to me?”

Joyce clenched his fists and held it to his mouth. He thought deep for a moment before saying, “I dreamed that I was falling from the Alfalfa into the ocean. The ocean was dark red, as if it was filled with rotting blood.

“As I fell, I was grabbed by a person on the boat. I could not identify him, but I know that he was very strong.

“And I was also holding onto a person in an attempt to save him from falling into the sea. I know that person. He was a passenger of the Alfalfa, Younis King.

“Because of his weight and his struggling, I could not bear the weight and could only release my hands and watch him get devoured by the sea of blood.

“At that moment, the person above me also released his hand. I flailed my arms, hoping to grab onto something, but there was nothing. I could only plummet rapidly.

“Then I wake up in horror, sweat covering my back and forehead.”

Klein held his forehead and gently rapped it as though he was thinking. He then organized his words and said, “Mr. Meyer, nightmares, similar nightmares, and repeated nightmares, these are all psychological problems and have a corresponding source. The same nightmare recurring time and time again is a reminder from your spirituality. It is also a revelation given to you by the divine.”

Upon seeing Joyce appearing confused, he elaborated, “Do not have any doubt, an ordinary person’s spirituality is also capable of giving reminders.

“I do not know what exactly happened on the Alfalfa, but I can see that it was a tragedy of blood and steel. It has left a deep trauma in you.”

Seeing Joyce nod slightly, Klein continued, “You must have been very horrified, very fearful on the ship. It is easy for a person to lose their observational skills when overwhelmed by such intense emotions; thus missing signs that they should not have missed. This does not mean that you have not seen those signs, but you have disregarded them, you understand? Disregarded.

“In your subconscious, in your spirituality, the details that you have missed are present all the same. If the thing that the detail is pointing toward is important enough, then your spirituality will remind you in the form of a dream.”

Previously, I had a similar case of disregarding a feeling, only to later realize that the diary was with Ray Bieber… But I was more sensitive and had stronger spirituality. I was also more knowledgeable about mysticism and thus could make a deduction more quickly… Klein paused for a few seconds and looked into Joyce Meyer’s eyes.

“Did Mr. Younis King—the one you let fall into the sea of blood—ask something of you on the boat, only to be unable to escape his fate?”

Joyce shifted uncomfortably, his movements stiff and unnatural. He opened his mouth several times before finally replying, “Yes, but I do not pity him. Perhaps in a few days, or a week at most, you will read in the newspapers how cruel and depraved he was. He raped and murdered at least three women, tossed a baby into the Berserk Sea, and led a band of deranged savages who slaughtered the ship’s passengers and crew.

“He was cunning, powerful, and vicious. I neither dared nor was able to stop him. To resist would only have been to throw away my life.”

“I am not questioning what you did,” Klein said, clarifying his stance. Then, in a calm voice, he continued, “But your dream tells me that you still feel regret and guilt. You believe you should not have let go of his hand. Since you consider killing him an act of justice, why then do you feel regret and remorse—so much so that you are haunted by recurring dreams of that very moment?”

“I don’t know…” Joyce shook his head, visibly confused.

Klein interlaced his fingers beneath his chin, his expression thoughtful as he began to analyze the situation.

“Incorporating what I just described, it seems you’ve overlooked certain details—such as what Younis King actually said, the contents of his plea, or even the way he carried himself. I cannot recall the memory for you, so think carefully.”

“There’s nothing… All he said was, ‘Spare me, I surrender…’” Joyce muttered, his face clouded with puzzlement.

Klein, not knowing the exact circumstances, could only guide him based on the fragments he had gleaned from the dream.

“Perhaps you felt Younis King was worth more alive—that he could prove something, or explain something?”

Joyce furrowed his brows. After a long pause, he said, “Perhaps… I still feel that the conflict aboard the Alfalfa broke out too suddenly, escalating far too quickly. It was as if the dormant evil in everyone’s hearts simply erupted, uncontrollable… It was too abnormal—far too abnormal. Perhaps I wanted to interrogate Younis King, to ask why he acted as though possessed by the devil in the first place…”

Hearing this dreamy confession, Klein suddenly caught hold of an inspiration. He leaned forward slightly, adopting that mysterious cadence unique to charlatans.

“No, that’s not the only reason.”

“What?” Joyce was visibly startled.

Klein interlaced his fingers and propped his chin upon them. Fixing Joyce with a steady, penetrating gaze, he said slowly, each word weighted, “Not only did you sense something abnormal—you also saw details you dismissed. And when pieced together, those neglected fragments point to a terrifying conclusion.

“Your spirituality is warning you. There is someone who deserves the gravest suspicion. That person is the one who seized your hand in the dream… yet let go in the end. You cannot recognize him because, deep down, you refuse to suspect him. He is your companion—the one who once held your fate in his hands, and perhaps… even saved your life before.”

Joyce leaned back suddenly, slamming into the back of the chair with a dull thud.

His forehead slowly became laced with sweat, his eyes filled with confusion.

“I… I see it…”

Joyce suddenly stood up noisily, causing his chair to wobble and nearly fall.

“Mr. Tris…” He used all the energy in him to utter the name.

He was a friendly and bashful little boy with a round face. He was the hero that saved the survivors…

Klein did not interrupt Joyce’s thoughts. He leaned back slightly and waited.

Joyce’s expression changed several times, finally returning to normal, a normal that had a little paleness.

He revealed a rueful smile.

“I understand now. Thank you for interpreting my dream. Perhaps it is time for me to make a trip to the police station.”

He took out his leather wallet and fished out a one-soli note.

“I do not think that money can fully represent your worth, and I can only give you the price you asked for. This is for you.” Joyce pushed the note toward Klein.

I wouldn’t have minded if you gave me ten pounds… One soli, you sure are like your fiancée… Klein kept up his mysterious vibe as a charlatan and said nothing, smiling as he pressed on the note.

Joyce took a deep breath, wore his hat, and turned to walk toward the door.

As he was unlocking the door, he suddenly turned back and said with sincerity, “Thank you, Master Moretti.”

Master? Klein laughed to himself. He watched as Joyce left the divination room and said silently to himself, Whatever happened on the Alfalfa seems extraordinary… If only the Captain was here. He would be able to understand everything that happened in Joyce Meyer’s dreams…

†

Tuesday at dawn. Backlund, Empress Borough.

Audrey, who woke up earlier, beckoned her golden retriever Susie over. She said with a serious tone, “Susie, you are also a Beyonder now. We are the same kind, ew—no, what I mean is that we have to help each other. Guard the door later and don’t let anyone disturb me. I have to conduct a ritual.”

Susie looked at her mistress and shook her tail in exasperation.

Chapter 64:
Instigator

After giving instructions to her golden retriever, Susie, Audrey paced back and forth, worry flickering in her eyes. She couldn’t be certain whether the ritualistic magic would trigger anything unusual.

“Let’s do this…” She steadied her breathing, forcing her thoughts into calm, and replayed the imagined process from the detached perspective of an observer. Soon, she settled on a new arrangement.

Audrey unlocked her bedroom door and said softly to Susie, “Stay here. If Annie or the others try to force their way in, run to the bathroom immediately and tell me.”

Her personal maidservant carried the spare key to her door out of precaution.

Susie gazed at her knowingly and wagged her tail three times.

“Very good. I’ll let you pick whatever you want for lunch today!” Audrey said with a gentle fist pump.

Having finished her exhortations, she entered the bathroom. The square bathtub inside spanned three to four meters on each side, filled with clear, gently rippling water that shimmered under drifting steam—a dreamlike sight.

Audrey straightened a rectangular table laden with bottles, then stepped back out to fetch candles, sacrificial items, and a white robe.

When everything was in place, she shut the bathroom door behind her.

With everything done, Audrey heaved a sigh of relief and picked up a translucent light-blue bottle beside the four candles.

The cylindrical bottle shimmered dreamily under the light. In it was the essence oils she had distilled from a mixture yesterday. As an enthusiast of mysticism, she had no lack of research regarding such items. She had many different kinds of extracts, flower essence, perfume, essential oils, and incense that she brewed herself at home. As such, she had already finished the initial preparations according to The Fool’s instructions.

“Moon flowers, gold mint, slumber flowers, fingered citron, and rock-rose… What an odd concoction…” Audrey mumbled softly. “Oh, one has to cleanse one’s body and calm their mind before engaging in ritualistic magic. This is a form of reverence to the divine—uh, to the target.”

As she went through the entire process in her head, she placed the ritual’s essential oil beside her bathtub. She reached out and began disrobing what she wore at home.

Pieces of her silk clothing fell into the laundry basket one after another. Audrey coiled up her hair into a bun and tested the water’s temperature with her hand. Then, she carefully stepped into the bathtub, allowing her body to slowly sink into the water’s warm embrace.

“Phew…” She exhaled comfortably, finding herself warm all over. She felt abnormally relaxed.

I don’t even want to move a single finger… Audrey rallied herself, snatching up the translucent light-blue bottle and letting a few drops of ritual oil fall into the water.

A waft of fragrance dispersed, filling the silence with a refreshing smell. Audrey breathed in a few times and nodded in satisfaction.

Not bad. It smells really good.

How relaxing. How comfortable…

I don’t want to move at all. All I wish is to lie here in silence…

Silence, in silence… si… lence…

After losing her sense of time, Audrey suddenly heard barking.

She opened her eyes in shock, looking to her sides in a daze. She had no idea when Susie had opened the door and entered. She was squatting outside the bathtub, looking at her with an exasperated look.

As she rubbed the corners of her eyes, Audrey felt that the water had cooled down quite significantly.

I-I fell asleep? She subconsciously asked herself.

Susie looked at her without barking or wagging her tail.

“Haha, the effects of that bottle of ritual essential oil sure is great. Yeah, really great!” Audrey chuckled dryly as she explained with a cheerful tone.

She stood up, retrieved a towel, and as she wrapped and wiped her body, said to the golden retriever beside her, “Susie, continue keeping watch. Do not let Annie and the rest enter!”

Only when the golden retriever left did she secretly stick out her tongue. She threw her towel aside and wore a clean white robe.

After closing the door to the bathroom, Audrey recalled the ritual she had memorized.

She picked up four candles and placed them on the four corners of the table.

A loaf of white bread at the top left corner, a bowl of Feynapotter noodles at the top right corner. Smells great, but it’s a little cold… No! It’s not time to think of this! Paella at the bottom left corner and Desi pie at the bottom right… Audrey set up the altar according to The Fool’s descriptions seriously, shaking her head twice during the process.

After she was done with the preparation, she left her four candles lit. She picked up a silver knife and stabbed it into a pile of coarse salt.

After narrating the sacred incantation in Hermes, Audrey raised the knife with beautiful patterns and placed it into a cup filled with clear water.

After focusing her mind, she pulled out the silver ‘sacred blade,’ cogitating her spirituality to spew out and spread from her blade.

Invisible energy spewed out as Audrey held the knife and circled the altar once. When she felt that a spirituality wall was fully erected around her, she expelled all the uncleanliness and distractions outside.

Maintaining her Spectator state, she prevented her excitement and joy from affecting the ritual.

She put down the silver knife and picked up the tiny light-blue crystalline bottle and dripped a drop on each candle.

Sizzle!

A faint fragrance emanated as Audrey’s body, heart, and soul seemed to attain tranquility.

She drew a breath as she lowered her head in reverence and began chanting the incantation in Hermes.

“The Fool that doesn’t belong to this era,

“You are the mysterious ruler above the gray fog,

“You are the King of Yellow and Black who wields good luck,

“I pray for your help.

“I pray for your loving grace.

“I pray for you to give me a good dream.

“Moon flower, a herb that belongs to the red moon, please bestow your powers to my incantation!

“Fingered citron, a herb that belongs to the sun, please bestow your powers to my incantation!”

†

Right after Audrey chanted the incantation and hoped to cogitate the contents of her plea, she felt there was a stir within the spirituality wall. She saw a dark red star swirling on the back of her hand.

Her heart leaped as she hurriedly closed her eyes and calmed her heart to plead sincerely.

When everything was over, she surveyed her surroundings wondrously, but did not find anything odd.

“Is that all?” Audrey knitted her eyebrows slightly as she whispered.

†

The King of Yellow and Black who wields good luck… The Fool that doesn’t belong to this era… In the Blue Avenger’s captain cabin, Alger Wilson in his windstorm robe was silently reciting the three lines of description he had heard in the afternoon. He seemed to be attempting to find clues of the person’s identity through it.

He shook his head and stood up in a clearly vexed manner, but ultimately did not do anything.

Alger was not at ease inside the Blue Avenger, an ancient ship that was a relic from the Tudor Dynasty. Although he was already in control of the ship, he had a gut feeling that there were still many hidden secrets, just like the Blood Emperor.

Therefore, he planned on using the ship to test The Fool’s powers but did not wish to attempt the unknown ritualistic magic on the ship.

Alger ruminated for a few minutes before leaving the captain’s cabin and went on deck. He said to the few sailors, “We will be reaching the Rorsted Archipelago soon. We will be anchoring there for a day.”

The sailors immediately cheered as they shouted in unison, “Thank you, My Lord!”

Since the ghost ship required no crew, only a handful of sailors were aboard. Supplies were never a concern, and they could dine on fresh food and drink clean water. Yet, the endless days at sea and the unchanging horizon wore them down both physically and mentally. It was as though they were constantly suppressing something, enduring in silence—until the pressure inside them boiled over.

As for the Rorsted Archipelago, it was a famous colony on the Sonia Sea. Their business was booming, and they had all kinds of industries.

“I simply can’t wait!” A crew member gyrated his hips and sniggered a meaningful laugh that all men would understand.

†

On the public carriage toward Zouteland Street, Klein, who was reading the newspapers leisurely, suddenly jolted. He seemed to hear an ethereal voice calling out to him.

Shapeless murmurs resounded in his mind as his forehead throbbed uncontrollably.

The contents of the calling that could not be heard left as fast as it came. In just ten seconds, it was gone. Klein pinched his forehead and resisted the throbbing pain deep in his brain.

Is this the murmurings of unknown existences that Old Neil mentioned? A result of having enhanced spiritual perception? Thoughts flashed through Klein’s mind as he suddenly saw four black dots appear on the back of his right hand. They were like tiny inconspicuous moles.

The four black dots that stemmed from the luck enhancement ritual quickly sank, dimmed, and vanished.

Klein looked at it in surprise and had an additional guess about what had just happened.

Justice or The Hanged Man has attempted the ritualistic magic I gave them?

Was my idea right?

Those three descriptions have precisely pointed towards me through the mysterious space above the gray fog?

But I’m far from powerful enough. I can’t hear the contents of their requests… I wonder if the information is ‘stored’ above the gray fog…

Yes, I should confirm it by entering tonight.

Klein felt a little perturbed and agitated. He quickly raised his newspaper and hid his face, preventing anyone from seeing the changes to his expression.

Soon, he arrived at Zouteland Street and entered the Blackthorn Security Company.

Before he could greet Rozanne, Klein saw Captain Dunn Smith walk out. He held a piece of paper with a portrait on it.

“Take a look at this internal warrant of arrest. A very cruel and vicious Beyonder has entered Tingen.” Dressed in his black trench coat, the hatless Dunn swept his gaze over and handed the piece of paper in passing.

Klein received it and the first thing that entered his vision was a portrait sketch.

The sketch was of boy with a round face. He looked amiable with a tiny hint of bashfulness and was fairly young, probably about eighteen or nineteen years old.

“Tris—a suspected Beyonder. Preliminary estimates place him as a Sequence 8 Instigator, and we cannot rule out the involvement of the Theosophy Order. He is believed to be responsible for the Alfalfa massacre… According to witness testimony, he traveled to Tingen after leaving Enmat Harbor. His current whereabouts remain unknown…”

Tris… Alfalfa… It’s actually a crime committed by a Beyonder? Klein suddenly recalled the dream interpretation from yesterday afternoon and Joyce Meyer’s description. He immediately said, “Captain, I know one of the witnesses. He might very well be an important witness.”

“I know. Joyce Meyer. My help was requested by the Machinery Hivemind last night. I saw you in Joyce’s dream. Many details have led to the confirmation that the Alfalfa tragedy was a result of Tris.” Dunn’s gray eyes looked unperturbed as he chuckled.

How uninteresting. Captain… thankfully it was my day off yesterday and not me acting as a Seer during working hours… Klein lampooned. He barely missed the horror of being caught moonlighting by his direct superior.

He asked instead, “Which Sequence pathway is Instigator? What kind of organization is the Theosophy Order?”

Is instigating others to kill each other the method Tris used to eliminate the side effects of the potion or is it a requirement needed to advance?

Dunn thought for a few seconds and said, “Coincidentally, it’s about time for you to learn the relevant information regarding Beyonders and the secret organizations. You shouldn’t be ordered by Old Neil to keep reading the historical documents all the time.”

Captain, wasn’t I recruited to be your ‘history expert’? Klein nodded earnestly, though he didn’t dare point out the problem.

“Alright.”

Chapter 65:
Beyonder Information

With a document signed by Dunn, Klein went underground and turned into the armory.

“Dunn is right. It’s time you understand the different Beyonders and the various secret organizations.” Dressed in a black classic robe, Old Neil read the note without finding it surprising. Instead, he supported the captain’s decision.

He then added immediately with a smile, “After all, you will be heading to the underground market with me tomorrow night.”

“Tomorrow night?” Klein did not conceal his pleasant surprise as he asked to confirm.

Old Neil nodded and said with a sigh, “I’m a person who can’t sleep when in debt. I always wish to settle them as soon as I can.”

You did not seem to act so previously. You left it to the last moment before using ritualistic magic to resolve the problem… So, I’m not the only one suffering from procrastination… Wait, is there a need to euphemize ‘afraid to spend the money used to repay a loan?’ Klein did not expose Old Neil and instead urged, “Mr. Neil, I’ll be troubling you to retrieve the corresponding information from Chanis Gate.”

The armory contained mostly archaeological and historical documents. A few texts touched on Beyonders and secret organizations, but they were rare—and for the most part, only covered basic knowledge.

Old Neil slowly took a sip from his hand-ground coffee and smacked his lips. He then walked out the armory with the signed and stamped document. Klein watched the place on his behalf.

About ten minutes later, Old Neil returned with a huge stack of documents.

“They can only be read here. They are not to be taken out,” he warned as he placed the information on the desk.

“Alright.” Klein gave a firm nod. He extended his hands and quickly flipped through the pages and did a general read through.

Very detailed… As expected of the Nighthawks’s internal documents… As expected of a Church with four thousand years of history or even more… Klein sighed inwardly as he glanced through the documents.

Not only did the documents introduce the various secret organizations, it also listed down many of the Sequence pathways. It was very complete. Some of them only wrote the potion name of the corresponding Sequence while others only described the Beyonder abilities of the corresponding Sequence. Some were completely missing and left blank.

While holding back his excitement, Klein found the Sequence pathway that led from Seer.

He ruffled through the pages and soon found a familiar word.

Then, his delighted expression quickly froze because there was no corresponding potion name—Sequences 7 and 8—after Seer!

Thankfully, the abilities of the two following Sequences are present… Klein silently exhaled as he calmed his mind and read the description seriously.

“Sequence 8: Potion name unknown. The corresponding Beyonder is good at fighting with artifice and very crafty.”

Good at fighting with artifice? This is the next advancement of Seer? Why does it feel odd… I’m not a hunter… Am I going to become a melee mage? What does crafty mean? My intelligence is enhanced, making me good at fooling the enemy? Klein was stunned. He even suspected that the Nighthawks’ information was wrong.

There were corresponding case studies appended, but he could not find a reasonable explanation despite reading it repeatedly.

He cast his gaze lower as the description of Sequence 7 entered his eyes.

“Potion name unknown. The corresponding Beyonder is good at many spells that can be cast quickly. Fuses one’s body’s skill and supernatural powers as one.

That’s more like it! This is what an advancement of a Seer should sound like! Klein heaved a sigh of relief.

After seeing the case studies of Sequence 7, he cast his eyes to the overall description of the pathway.

“This Sequence pathway was first established by the Solomon Empire’s Zaratul family. During the conflicts of the Fourth Epoch, the family was not fully destroyed. The family’s name was occasionally heard in the history of the Fifth Epoch… It is suspected to be connected to the ancient organization, the Secret Order.”

Zaratul? Upon seeing this name, Klein’s eyes constricted.

He had just seen this name appear in the remnant diary pages of Emperor Roselle yesterday afternoon!

Roselle’s acting method was inspired by a tip from the mysterious figure known as Zaratul!

Because of that mysterious Zaratul, Emperor Roselle regretted not choosing Seer? And so I was indirectly influenced, becoming a Seer myself. The acting method thus returns to the hands of a Seer… It all feels strangely predestined… Klein knitted his brows, sensing that something about the situation was off.

Just from the logical chain, he did not feel that there was anything wrong in any aspect. However, in the domain of mysticism, pre-destiny often manifested things and involved new problems.

In addition, transmigration is quite a baffling matter… It’s just confusing… And the guy I’ve possessed tried to commit suicide because of the lost notebook of the Secret Order… Klein thought for quite a while and had many guesses, but lacked the information needed to prove them.

Phew… After repeatedly reading the information, he finally suppressed his ideas and read the other records.

He first found the Sailor Sequence and discovered that it indeed belonged to the Lord of Storms.

For an old opponent that they haven’t faced for perhaps more than two to three thousand years, the Nighthawks’s internal records were rather detailed.

“Sequence 8: Folk of Rage. Ancient name—Guardian of the Storm. The corresponding Beyonder can release several strikes that exceed ordinary thresholds when enraged. Their strength and speed are greatly enhanced… Facing them is like facing a storm…

“Sequence 7: Seafarer. Ancient name—Storm Priest. The corresponding Beyonder is also a scholar of astronomy and geography. They have an intuitive grasp of magnetic fields, ocean currents, wind direction, and clouds… A boat with a Seafarer will never get lost at sea… They are even more beloved by the oceans and gain enhancements in every aspect at sea…

“They are friends of water. They can act freely underwater for more than half an hour… They can cast a limited number of water-related spells. Some are a result of their own capabilities and some are a boon from the Lord of Storms, for example…”

A Sequence 7 Seafarer is very powerful… Klein nodded while in deep thought.

He suspected that The Hanged Man was a Guardian of the Storm, if not a Seafarer. From how he has recently advanced, it was more likely he was the latter.

This also indicated in a way that The Hanged Man was either a member of the Mandated Punisher or a pirate who had been secretly absorbed by the Church of Storms.

Impressive. Impressive… Klein flipped back a few pages and found the advancement of Spectator. He discovered that the description was identical to what The Hanged Man had said.

Sequence 9 Spectators were like Seers. They lacked direct combat means and could only observe a target to obtain information, gleaning the true thoughts of the target. By doing so, they could provide subtle influences and guidance to cause situations to develop in a way they wished.

Sequence 8 Telepathist was the advancement of Spectator. Their observation was not only limited to superficial details, but deeper into one’s aura, Ether Body, or other domains in mysticism. The combination of the two allowed a Telepathist to precisely understand a person’s thoughts as though they could read their minds. It was difficult to have any secrets before them.

Sequence 7 Psychiatrist, which was also known as Psyche Analyst, had further enhancements above the Sequence 8 foundations—now capable of directly influencing a target. For instance, they could treat a target’s maniacal problems or alternatively, cause them to turn maniacal and lose their reason.

“A Beyonder that is very difficult to be noticed…” After reading the description, Klein made a reasoned judgment.

After understanding the relevant information concerning the Gathering members, he flipped to the Church of the God of Steam and Machinery. This was because Emperor Roselle had chosen their Savant Sequence.

“Sequence 9: Savant. The corresponding Beyonder believes that knowledge is power. They have a rough understanding of the supernatural, but are more knowledgeable about aqua regia, nitroglycerin, and complicated bolts and gears. They seem to know everything.”

No wonder Emperor Roselle said this potion suited him perfectly, letting him press his advantage to the fullest… Klein understood completely as his gaze dropped.

After the description of several case studies, the corresponding Sequence 8 finally appeared in Klein’s vision.

“Archaeologist. They possess a good deal of knowledge about history and outdoor survival, as well as forbidden knowledge about ruins. They have a strong enough body and ability to face everything…”

“Sequence 7: Appraiser. They can intuitively understand the powers and problems of most extraordinary items, and can use them while minimizing danger…”

As Klein’s security clearance was insufficient, he only had access to Sequence pathways up to 7. It left him a little frustrated, but there was no other way around it. He only wished that Backlund would quickly send over Sealed Artifact 2-049 to determine if Ray Bieber was a descendant of the Antigonus family.

That way, he would have a chance of becoming a formal member and obtain a higher security clearance.

Collecting himself, Klein read the material seriously from cover to cover. He knew that the sequences following Corpse Collector were Gravedigger and Spirit Medium. He also knew that there was no information about Sequence 8 of the Mystery Pryer pathway. Not only was there no name for the potion, but even the description had been left blank. There was a name for Sequence 7 of that pathway: Warlock!

Sounds impressive… Klein slowly flipped the page and saw Apprentice and Marauder which Emperor Roselle had lingering thoughts for. Their records only reached Sequence 8 and nothing more.

“Sequence 9: Apprentice. Their abilities are rather strange. It can only be confirmed that this is the originating pathway of a mage. They are rarely trapped and very difficult to be stopped. They often are able to escape and pass through obstacles every time…

“Sequence 8: Trickmaster. They wield all kinds of strange but impotent spells…”

“Sequence 9: Marauder. Difficult to separate these Beyonders from ordinary bandits or thieves. Perhaps the means available to them are more impressive, but their goal of stealing riches is not for enjoyment or survival. It’s more like answering a calling…”

“Sequence 8: Swindler. We have discovered traces of such Beyonders in fraud investigations. They gain enjoyment from swindling…”

Gain enjoyment from swindling… This is ‘acting’ in a different form, isn’t it? If I had the choice, I might have chosen Apprentice… Klein silently said to himself. Suddenly, he discovered the corresponding Sequence potion of the culprit of the Alfalfa tragedy, Tris—Instigator.

Chapter 103:
Doing As the Heart Willed

He resides at 19 Howes Street?

Whilst memorizing the information, Klein keenly noticed a piece of information.

Yes, Welch stayed on Howes Street. The Divination Club is on Howes Street. This cloth merchant named Sirius Arapis also lives on Howes Street… From the looks of it, it’s nothing strange for Welch to know Hanass Vincent either. They might have even gotten to know each through Sirius Arapis…

Suddenly, Klein felt that he had linked the clues together as his thoughts turned clear.

He was originally confused as to how Welch would be acquainted with Hanass Vincent since this son of a banker wasn’t particularly interested in mysticism. To him, money was more important than divinations. But now, Klein felt that he had an inkling as to how they became acquainted.

According to the descriptions of several magazines, middle-class and wealthy residents would gladly pay a visit to their neighbors from the same social class in order to form a social circle which is beneficial to them. Similarly, Welch and the cloth merchant, Sirius, absolutely have the motivation and opportunity to become friends since they both lived in the Howes Street vicinity…

It isn’t hard to understand how Sirius knew Hanass Vincent, who regularly went to the Divination Club on Howes Street. Perhaps it was a coincidental meeting, or perhaps Hanass had helped him out before. Regardless, this made it possible for the two of them, who frequently ran into each other within the same area, to become closer to one another….

Hanass Vincent wanted to sell his ancient books, and thus, Sirius introduced him to Welch, who was an undergraduate of the History department…

In Hanass’ dream, there was the figure of the suspected evil god, the “True Creator.” He also knew of the proper incantation format. This proves that he was very deep into the realm of mysticism. The possibility that he might have even been a member of some secret organization cannot be dismissed.

I cannot rule out the possibility of him joining some secret organization under Sirius’s influence.

†

With ideas coming to him so easily, Klein could tell that the information the man had left behind had a certain level of credibility without even using divination methods.

Even if he isn’t called Sirius Arapis, nor work as a cloth merchant, and doesn’t live at 19 Howes Street, he definitely resides at Howes Street or, at the very least, somewhere nearby!

While these ideas ran through his mind, Klein viewed the borrowing records once again with this new train of thought.

The last time he came to Deweyville Library was last Saturday, a day before Selena’s birthday party, which was also a day before Hanass Vincent died. Several days have already passed since then, but he hasn’t returned the issues that he borrowed.

According to past records, if he only borrowed two issues, he would usually return them the next day.

Could this mean that he knows of Hanass’ death and was scared to the point that he no longer dares to come to the Deweyville Library again?

Yes, he started by borrowing several unrelated history books and journals until he narrowed down what he needed, which is very similar to what I had read…

This means that there was no one teaching him. There was no Senior Associate Professor from the history department of a university. He did this completely through trial and error.

What would a shocked target do? Two choices. One, if he had all the necessary information, he would head straight to the main peak of the Hornacis mountain range. Two, if he still lacks information, he would lay low and observe the situation. He would only show himself again if he’s certain that Hanass’ death wouldn’t implicate him.

Having made this conclusion, Klein closed the borrowing records and returned them to the librarians. He then took out the portrait and asked if anyone had seen the man. Unfortunately, many people came to borrow books every day, and the librarians didn’t have any impression of the average person.

“Alright, thank you for your time.” Klein put away his identification documents and his badge.

He had no intention of continuing the investigation alone. This wasn’t only dangerous, but also troublesome. He planned to head to Zouteland Street once again and hand the case over to Captain and his teammates. He then planned to go home and prepare his Tomato Oxtail Soup for his siblings before heading to the world above the gray fog to divine the target’s whereabouts and condition.

“Officer, is there anything else?” a librarian asked sincerely as he heaved a sigh of relief.

Klein nodded slightly and answered, “No, I will come back if there are new clues.”

He held his black cane with his left hand and made his way to the door.

At this moment, he saw a man enter the library with his head hung low. He was dressed in a double-breasted coat, its collars standing tall.

When they walked past each other, Klein caught a glance of his thick, messy brows, and his pair of grayish-blue eyes!

These were things the tall collar couldn’t hide!

Sirius? Sirius Arapis? A coincidence? Klein froze. He didn’t expect to meet his target here!

What kind of luck was this!

Wasn’t this too much of a coincidence?

He evaluated his physical condition and felt his aching sore muscles. Thus, he acted as though nothing had happened and continued walking towards the door.

Well, we have to follow what our heart tells us! Safety matters!

It doesn’t matter if I missed this opportunity as long as Sirius is still in Tingen!

At this moment, the man in the double-breasted coat arrived before the counter and was handing the journals to one of the librarians.

“It’s a return,” he said with a soft, muffled tone.

The librarian received the journals causally and when he saw it, he suddenly froze.

He subconsciously looked up and differently as his body couldn’t help but tremble.

“Is there a problem?” the man asked in a deep voice.

His question seemed like a spark that ignited a fuse, causing the librarian to instantly lose his self-control. He sprinted to the side and shouted,

“Officer!”

“The criminal is here!”

At this moment, Klein, who hadn’t left the building, cursed madly in his heart.

He instinctively reached for his holster with his right hand and drew his revolver.

That man froze for a moment before turning and breaking into a sprint.

But he didn’t head for the door. Instead, he escaped in the direction of the oriel window to the side, as if he wanted to smash through the glass and jump out onto the street.

Klein, who was flustered, turned his head to see the scene when he felt a sudden calm.

He realized that even though he was afraid of the target, his target was more afraid of him!

The man must be unable to determine my abilities in such an abrupt meeting. He isn’t clear on what I am adept in, and so, he will instinctively avoid a direct confrontation and look for other ways to escape! Confident of his analysis, Klein lifted his revolver and pulled the trigger.

At that moment, the man in the double-breasted coat abruptly rolled onto the ground in an attempt to avoid the bullet.

Following up on that, he pressed down on the ground with his right hand and propelled himself into the air towards the oriel window.

Click! Klein’s first shot was empty.

But this was something he had expected. He took advantage of Sirius’s inability to dodge while in midair to aim at his torso and pulled the trigger.

Bang!

The silver demon hunting bullets tore through the air and penetrated straight through Sirius’s back.

Crash! The glass shattered and Sirius flew out the window, leaving drops of crimson blood on the crystalline glass fragments and windowsill.

Klein was no longer afraid now that the target was injured. He ran over and jumped out the window with the help of a chair.

This was the area lining the back of Deweyville Library’s ground floor. A row of trees isolated a lush green field.

The injured Sirius was running to the side, in an attempt to enter a small alley between two buildings. Having not practiced shooting at moving targets, Klein didn’t dare to fire blindly. He could only carry his cane in one hand and his gun in the other as he pursued the man in a black coat.

Tap! Tap! Tap!

He followed the trail of blood on the floor and tried to close the distance.

With a corner coming up, the injured Sirius’s speed became slower and slower. Klein, who had been waiting for an opportunity to capture him, suddenly felt a little afraid. He felt as though the man in front of him wasn’t human, but a wolf or a tiger, one that harbored terrifying dangers.

This was an instinct he had as a Seer, and also a warning given to him by his spirituality!

Klein immediately slowed down, his eyes scanning the blood on the ground.

Compared to the blood he had seen earlier, Sirius’s blood was now black!

At this moment, a violent wind overwhelmed him. Sirius’s face was reflected in Klein’s eyes.

Thick, messy brows. Grayish blue eyes. Multiple protruding warts. An open mouth with two rows of white teeth.

Sirius was launching a counterattack at this moment!

This made the face reflected in Klein’s eyes more visible. He could even smell a particularly putrid stench!

Sirius pounced a distance of seven or eight meters, far more than any normal human being could jump. But as Klein had stopped chasing him just in time, there was still a distance of nearly ten meters between them.

When the distance was shortened to two meters, the sticky saliva caused by drool and the disgusting dense warts formed a harrowing scene that made Klein’s nerves tense up.

Without thinking, he seized the opportunity of the temporary immobility caused by Sirius’s pounce to raise his right hand. He fired without stopping, allowing the bullets to rain down on the target’s head.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

Shooting from such a close distance allowed the silver demon hunting bullets to drill through Sirius’s head. Blood splattered everywhere as his face became more and more mangled, until he staggered backwards.

Klein had emptied the bullets in his revolver in an instant. He subconsciously wanted to take a few steps back in order to confirm the results of this battle.

But at this moment, Sirius gave Klein the shock of his life by trying his hardest to stand up straight. Klein abruptly lifted the cane in his left hand.

Smack! The sturdy silver-inlaid black cane struck Sirius’s neck, leaving a dark red mark.

Smack! Smack! Smack!

Klein acted on instinct, raining blows on his opponent until Sirius collapsed stumbling onto the ground.

Huff! Puff! Huff! Klein supported himself with his cane and took deep breaths. His eyes were trained intently on his target, afraid that Sirius would suddenly jump back to life.

At that moment, Sirius’ head had basically been smashed into a pulp, and the warts gradually receded. His body stopped moving after a few convulsions.

Klein was in no hurry to examine the corpse. Instead, he tossed his cane to the side and took out the demon hunting bullets he had on him and reloaded his revolver.

After doing this, he collected himself and fought back his disgust, kneeling down to search the pockets of Sirius’s double-breasted coat.

Chapter 168:
Clown Potion

Phew, I finally passed… I passed it just like that…

When Klein heard Crestet Cesimir’s announcement, he let out a breath of relief despite being mentally prepared for it. It felt surreal, as though it was a dream.

He had assumed that the examination would be tougher and lengthier, but when he thought carefully about it, he realized that what had just happened was what should’ve happened. If he had taken the normal three years to digest the Seer potion instead of doing it in a month, the examination wouldn’t have even been conducted by the Holy Cathedral. The Tingen Nighthawks’ captain would’ve been responsible for it instead.

I thought they would investigate my family and friends… Hmm, perhaps Cesimir arrived in Tingen two days ago and completed that in secret… I also thought that the examination would require me to complete some task. Heh, I was really overthinking it. The goal of the examination is merely to determine the level of digestion for the potion, as well as detect any latent dangers, and see whether I’m aware of the “acting method” and if I shared my experience with others… These thoughts flew past Klein’s mind. He flashed a sincere smile.

“Thank you, Your Grace. Praise the Lady!”

Crestet nodded gently and said, “To advance is to serve the Goddess better, so that you can protect our fellow believers better. You must remember this—trust me—it’ll help you fight the temptation of losing control.”

“Temptation…” Klein ruminated over the word.

Crestet sized Klein up with his green eyes and said sternly, “The ‘acting method’ can help you digest the potion and lower the risk of losing control, but it’s not the be-all and end-all. To a certain extent, you can even confuse playing the role and your own existence. You know, there are many actors in the theater that develop severe psychological issues. At a certain level, you might really go insane.”

Remember that you’re only acting… The only point of note concluded by the City of Silver is identical to what Deacon Cesimir said… Klein nodded thoughtfully in agreement.

“In addition,” Crestet emphasized, “Not only is losing control related to the potion, it’s also closely related to your emotions and mental health. The most important thing for a Beyonder is to control yourself. Only then will you be able to withstand the temptations of evil gods and devils, resisting emotions like greed and jealousy, and the erosion of desire. Of course, I don’t mean that you should get rid of all your emotions and desires, because that is something that no human or even demigod can do. Yes, perhaps only some special Sequences are able to achieve that sort of state.”

Klein suddenly thought about Old Neil. He couldn’t help but ask in reply, “We must keep our emotions and desires at a reasonable level, and not allowing them to drive us to do something irrational and abnormal?”

Crestet nodded solemnly.

“Yes.”

After he answered, there were wrinkles at the corner of his eyes.

“That’s all I wanted to warn you about. Now, I’ll pass you the Clown potion formula and the relevant ingredients.”

He bent down and put his silver suitcase on the long table. He then turned around and moved a few steps, blocking Klein’s view.

When the surrounding lights strangely vanished again, Klein suddenly understood that the formula and ingredients were in the suitcase that stored the holy artifact. It was simply because his gaze was attracted by the pure white bone sword which was why he didn’t notice or perhaps, he couldn’t notice, the other items in the suitcase.

After a few minutes, the light of the gas lamps lit up the alchemy room again. Crestet picked up his suitcase and moved away, presenting the items on the long table to Klein.

Among them, the most eye-catching item was the palm-sized gray goat horn. It looked like a miniature version of a normal goat horn and was crystal clear, swirling with colors. There were faint layers of unique patterns.

Next to the goat horn was a blue rose. There were red veins on the petals that connecting them together. It seemed to form a human face with a smile.

Hahaha, woowoowoo, hahaha, woowoowoo… Klein heard illusory laughter and crying diffused with each other, and he saw pieces of gray halos floating in midair.

A crystal of the single horn of a matured Hornacis gray mountain goat and a complete stalk of a human-faced rose. The main ingredients of the Clown potion! He nodded indiscernibly and took a few steps towards the long table.

“80 milliliters of pure water, 5 drops of tornapple juice, 7 grams of black-rimmed sunflower powder, 10 grams of golden cloak grass powder, 3 drops of poison hemlock…” Klein looked at the unfurled goatskin parchment and compared the written content with the formula that he had memorized.

After he confirmed that there was nothing wrong, he recalled the demonstration Old Neil did.

He took a deep breath and exhaled slowly to collect his emotions. With the apparatus in the alchemy room, he distilled some pure water needed by the potion.

In the potion formula, pure water referred to water that was distilled over and over again.

Then, he washed a black metal pot and threw in the supplementary ingredients one after another. He was as skillful as back when he had done chemistry experiments in high school.

As the Beyonder ingredients hadn’t catalyzed just yet, he didn’t see any obvious changes in the liquid in the metal pot. At most, he only saw powder floating on the surface of the liquid.

When he was done with the preparations, Klein cast his gaze at the two main ingredients and gratefully thought, There’s no description of the exact size or weight of the required gray mountain goat’s single horn crystal or the human-faced rose. Perhaps a whole horn and a complete rose have no differences, regardless of their weight, allowing them to meet the requirements… Yes, in the world of mysterious Beyonders, this is definitely possible…

If so, I don’t have to worry about putting in excessive amounts of the main ingredients!

After a few seconds, Klein picked up the human-faced rose and threw it into the metal pot.

When the strange flower touched the liquid, it immediately produced a sizzling sound. The surrounding illusory laughter became shrill.

Hahaha, hahaha!

Klein didn’t delay any further as he immediately grabbed the crystalline mountain goat horn and threw it into the metal pot.

Poof!

The terrifying laughter disappeared all of a sudden, and the surrounding gray halos slowly converged into the metal pot.

Klein lowered his head and saw the liquid in the pot was colored in a mix of gold, yellow, and red. However, the three colors remained extremely distinct at their boundaries.

There were bubbles churning and fizzing from the liquid, but they failed to escape from the pot and ended up bursting silently.

The scene reminded Klein of Sprite, the carbonated drink from his previous incarnation.

This actually looks like a delicious drink… A thought popped into his head that aligned with the characteristics of his culture.

Suppressing his nervousness, excitement, and anticipation, Klein poured the liquid from the black metal pot into a glass bottle.

What shocked him was that there wasn’t a single bit of the potion left in the metal pot.

It really is a potion that turns people into Beyonders… Klein raised his right hand, and he looked at the beautiful-looking tri-colored liquid.

Crestet Cesimir, who had been silent the entire time, suddenly smiled and said, “Don’t worry. At the very least, I didn’t notice any problems with the concoction of your potion.

“I’ve been waiting here to ensure that no accidents happen after you consume the potion. Don’t worry, as long as it isn’t anything serious, I should be able to save you.”

Okay. Klein nodded and placed the Clown potion back onto the long table.

Then, he took off the silver chain inside his sleeve and let the topaz pendant hang down naturally, a slight distance above the liquid.

To Beyonders of any other occupation, pendulum divinations could only divine a yes or no answer. Of course, when there wasn’t enough information, the divination wouldn’t yield any useful answers at all. When the pendulum didn’t spin, it was called a failed divination.

As a Seer, Klein’s pendulum could also vaguely determine the degree of the “yes” or “no” answer.

Klein’s eyes grew dark as he recited, “This potion is harmful.

“This potion is harmful.”

†

Seven times later, he opened his half-closed eyes and saw the topaz pendant spinning clockwise, but very slowly.

Clockwise means a positive response. In other words, it means that the potion is harmful… However, it spins slowly, which means that it’s only slightly harmful… Yes, potions can bring about a loss of control, so there’s the possibility of harm. A low level of harm means there is nothing wrong with the potion… Klein let out a breath of relief and wound the pendulum on his left wrist before covering it with his sleeve.

At that moment, Crestet couldn’t help but sigh.

“…You really are a professional Seer.”

“I must fully utilize my advantage, but I can’t rely on it too much and think that it’s all-powerful,” Klein replied softly and took up the Clown potion bottle.

After drinking it, I’ll become a Sequence 8 Beyonder…

The thought flashed in his mind and Klein didn’t hesitate. He raised the bottle, tipped his head, and gulped down the potion.

Bitter! So bitter!

It sucks, totally!

He instantly realized what it meant to look good on the outside, but rotten on the inside. His face had contorted as a result of the potion. He wanted to puke, but he couldn’t.

Then, Klein realized that his face was flushed red. As for the rest of his body, they were experiencing a similar reaction.

He was convinced that he looked like a steamed lobster. As for his spirit and mind, they felt like they had been extracted into a thin needle, fusing with the potion, drop by drop, as it stabbed into each and every one of cells.

It was a feeling that needed no microscope to observe his cells. Klein stood there and “saw” the intruder invade his body’s most minute areas.

For a few seconds, he felt like a robot that was having its parts and electrical circuits swapped out.

After an unknown period of time had passed, his mind reflected his figure, as though he was listening to himself singing through his own ears.

Due to this strange projection, Klein discovered that he could precisely control his facial and bodily motions.

Meanwhile, his ears buzzed. He heard the murmurs and shouting echoing around him which had not happened in a while.

Hornacis… Flegrea… Hornacis… Flegrea… Hornacis… Flegrea…

Phew. Klein imagined the layered spherical light and slowly entered a Cogitation state. Bit by bit, he escaped from the state of having his spirituality seep out where he had a slight loss of control.

At that moment, he knew that he had advanced successfully. He knew that he was a Sequence 8 Clown.

Chapter 210:
Story

In a Tingen suburb, there was a house with a green lawn.

The house had a garden that had begun to wither at the beginning of September. Attached to the house was a crimson chimney.

There was a desk next to the window in the bedroom of that house. An ordinary notebook was spread open on the table.

A slightly pale hand flipped the notebook to the very first page, then it quickly flipped to the back.

As the paper flipped, the rows of words appeared faintly.

Regence, a member from the Secret Order, sold the Antigonus family’s notebook as an ordinary ancient book by accident due to the influence of both weariness and illusions. It was a coincidence that made logical sense.

Affected by the calling of the Antigonus family’s bloodline, the notebook secretly affects its owners, one after the other. After repeated changes in ownership, it came to Tingen. It fell into the hands of the members of the Aurora Order—Sirius Arapis and Hanass Vincent.

After they flipped through the content that temporarily appeared in the notebook and copied the corresponding potion formulas, Sirius and Hanass were worried that the Secret Order, who were good at divination, would track them down. After discussing it, they decided to avoid the risk by selling it to another person.

They didn’t wait for Mr. Z’s reply; perhaps because he stayed at Enmat Harbor.

Through Sirius’s introduction, Hanass got to know Welch McGovern from the Khoy University’s Department of History. Then, Hanass sold the Antigonus family’s notebook to McGovern as an ordinary ancient book.

Subsequently, Sirius was attracted by the treasure that was said to exist on the main peak of the Hornacis mountain range. He started to visit the Deweyville Library and research the mountain. He didn’t think that there would be any problems, so he left his real address and name. That aligned with his personality.

During this process, he acquainted himself with Lanevus, who was reading up on information about iron mines to set up a scam.

Lanevus’s hidden lunacy and swindling ability were well appreciated by Sirius. He decided to nurture him into a member of the Aurora Order. Of course, before that, an investigation was inevitable.

Sirius covertly informed Lanevus about the evil ritual of praying to the True Creator to deliver “His” spawn into this world. But he knew that the possibility of Lanevus succeeding was very low, because the difficulty level of the ritual was very high, and the requirements were very harsh. However, the latter expressed his strong interest in the matter, tempted by the possibility of obtaining a deity’s approval. He planned to complete the ritual simultaneously as he carried out the plans of establishing his steelworks company.

The cunning Lanevus could tell that there was something fishy about Sirius Arapis. But for his personal goal, he didn’t expose him.

He visited Hood Eugen in the asylum once again. They had known each other long ago, and they knew about their respective situations.

After a dark divination, the Antigonus family’s notebook was awakened fully. Welch and his classmate died. The lucky survivor, Klein Moretti, sent it to Ray Bieber’s house under the influence of the notebook. It was a destined ending.

Many rows were scribbled off and new content followed.

For some baffling reason, and a lack of sufficient explanations, Klein didn’t commit suicide after that and somehow managed to stay alive.

In the Nighthawks’ investigation of Welch’s case that followed, he met Dunn Smith and joined the Nighthawks.

Although it had already exceeded Ince Zangwill’s description, it didn’t affect the development of the story.

Bacchus and his brothers were down on their luck. They lost their last chip at the gambling tables and were drowning in debt. In a bid to obtain money, they decided to kidnap and blackmail the somewhat wealthy individuals.

When they were looking for their final hideout, they chanced upon the room opposite Ray Bieber’s apartment.

By then, Ray Bieber was already seduced by the power offered by the Antigonus family’s notebook. He hoped to digest the gift left behind by his ancestors.

However, he was in a semi-insane state, and he couldn’t make the best and safest choice. He abandoned his dead mother, but he continued remaining in Tingen City. He only found a more elusive spot to carry out his digestion ritual. It was truly pathetic. If he had been slightly smarter, the story could’ve become even more complicated, but his decision was made based on his instincts and his poor state of mind.

Bacchus and company purchased weapons and took the youngest son, Elliott, of the tobacco merchant, Vickroy, and held him for ransom.

Finally, they successfully carried out the abduction and took Elliot back to the apartment opposite Ray Bieber’s. Vickroy’s butler was entrusted with looking for help from a security company.

Because of Welch’s mysterious death, security companies were short on hands. Klee chanced upon a deliveryman and happened to discover the existence of the Blackthorn Security Company.

Leonard Mitchell and Klein accepted the job. Relying on their Beyonder powers, they quickly saved the merchant’s son. Regrettably, Klein didn’t immediately realize that clues to the Antigonus family’s notebook were in the apartment opposite them.

However, his spirituality reminded him in his dream. As such, the Tingen Nighthawks discovered corresponding clues.

†

Sealed Artifact 2-049 arrived in Tingen. With the aid of the Antigonus family’s puppet, Dunn Smith led the Nighthawks to find Ray Bieber before interrupting his digestion procedure.

Ray Bieber became a monster, and the situation was out of control.

In the end, the Nighthawks skillfully worked together and took care of Monster Bieber, but they immediately faced the attack of a member from the Secret Order.

More rows were scribbled away again, and the original content was impossible to read.

Leonard Mitchell, who possesses a secret, was going to end the situation. Before he could, Klein, who was supposed to be doomed, killed the Sequence 7 member from the Secret Order in an inexplicable manner.

That didn’t affect the development of the story. Dunn Smith got in touch with the Antigonus family’s notebook and flipped through its content. From that point onwards, he was secretly corrupted!

†

Having finished with all his preparations, Lanevus beguiled Hood Eugen and used him to assist in his ritual. They tricked Lanevus’s fiancée, Megose, to become the vessel that would carry the True Creator’s spawn.

Lanevus had almost no possibility of success. The most serious problem was that even though Megose would be protected by the ritual’s power, she wouldn’t be able to withstand the sexual intercourse with the illusory projection of a deity. It would cost her her life on the altar.

At that moment, the kind Ince Zangwill helped Lanevus in secret. He split off half a piece of a descendant of Death’s characteristic that he obtained and planted it into Megose’s body ahead of time.

Hood Eugen made Megose enter a semi-unconscious state and convinced her that the True Creator’s illusory projection was Lanevus. Nourished by the accumulated resentment, gloominess, and oppression of the factory district, the ritual succeeded. Megose was pregnant with the True Creator’s spawn. The deity saw through the coincidences, but since “He” wished to break through the shackles placed on him by the seven deities, “He” didn’t refuse.

Hood Eugen was contaminated.

After the ritual succeeded, the mad Lanevus regained his rationality. He clearly knew that if the deity’s spawn was to descend into the world, Lanevus, himself, would become one of the sacrificial offerings. How could a mortal be the father of a deity’s son? This was blasphemy of the highest order!

Lanevus decided to leave Tingen ahead of time and left clues to the Nighthawks, the Mandated Punishers, and the Machinery Hivemind so that they could resolve the repercussions of his actions. There was ultimately a price needed for lunacy.

However, Lanevus didn’t write the letter directly to the Beyonder squads. He thought it would make him look stupid.

He decided to leave the letter in one of the houses that he rented. He pretended to be playing a game with the Beyonders from official bodies. As such, he didn’t bring up Hood Eugen’s contamination and brought with him everything that he had obtained.

Just in case, he informed Sirius Arapis in the safest way he could. The latter didn’t quite believe him, but he could faintly feel the possibility of success.

†

Selena Wood accidentally chanced upon the real Magic Mirror Divination incantation from her mysticism teacher, Hanass Vincent.

Her bold attempt was interrupted by Klein Moretti by coincidence. The latter successfully resolved this supernatural incident that might’ve caused serious casualties.

The Nighthawks then investigated Hanass Vincent who had recently been awarded. Therefore, Dunn Smith coincidently saw a clear image of the True Creator in his dream and suffered severe injuries.

However, he wasn’t contaminated because of what happened. That would’ve been noticed by the upper echelons of the Nighthawks.

The injury made Dunn Smith’s contamination by the Antigonus family notebook worsen. His absent-mindedness and forgetfulness worsened, and he was getting closer and closer to satisfying Ince Zangwill’s requirements.

†

Many rows were scribbled away again.

Seriously unbelievable! Klein Moretti noticed Ince Zangwill’s secret influence and saw the crimson chimney.

Th-This is because he was reminded by the teacher from the Khoy University’s Department of History, Azik. He possesses many secrets.

But even so, it’s astounding enough for Klein to discover actual clues. It’s unexplainable.

Regardless of the reason, Ince Zangwill continued to act, and the story continues.

Klein coincidently ran into Sirius at the library and had no choice but to kill him. Hence, the clues leading to Lanevus were abruptly severed, and the discovery of the problem was delayed.

†

Klein met Megose, but his spirituality stopped him from observing her closely. However, he didn’t notice the subtle abnormality. That is logical. Our stories aren’t made up randomly.

He searched for the red chimney, but he always opted for a route that didn’t include his target. Maybe in another two or three months, when he was on the last batch, he would find the real red chimney house.

†

Rows and rows of writings were scribbled away, more than all of the previous rows added together.

Dunn Smith’s problem was alleviated! His condition obviously became better! He actually mastered the “acting method!”

And this was taught to him by Klein Moretti, who found inspiration from Daly Simone and Old Neil’s example. No—Ince Zangwill didn’t believe that, but he could only change his original plans slightly.

New elements in the story came to play.

Azik decided to go to Backlund in search of his lost memories.

It wasn’t long until Klein and Dunn found clues from Hood Eugen.

†

In order to ensure that Tingen City’s Conservative Party and New Party would be in complete opposition, Madam Sharon, who wanted to vent the accumulated madness after her transformation, decided to take the risk and murder Member of Parliament John Maynard.

“Her motive wasn’t strong enough, but she took action anyway. There are always times when people are not clear-minded enough, and she happened to be in that stage. Besides, she was confident that she wouldn’t be discovered.

Maynard’s wife found the Blackthorn Security Company through the tobacco merchant, Vickroy. They didn’t disappoint her, and they quickly found Madam Sharon’s abnormality.

Dunn Smith, who possessed power that was close to Sequence 6, decided to take action first. He passed the Sealed Artifact 3-0271 to Kenley.

When the two of them and Klein returned to Madam Sharon’s residence, Dunn attempted to pull her into a dream to control her from a distance.”

It was a good plan, but, unfortunately, Madam Sharon happened to have the statue of the Primordial Demoness by her side.

Hence, the Nighthawks’ plan failed. Kenley reflected himself in the mirror due to his nervousness and saw himself.

Madam Sharon was taken care of while Kenley died. Dunn blamed himself and consumed Kenley’s Beyonder characteristic as he usually did. His digestion procedure was interrupted as a result and was delayed. As such, his mental state became unstable.

Under the circumstances, Leonard and Klein noticed the letter left behind by Lanevus.

Megose received a baffling summoning and arrived at Zouteland Street. She entered the Blackthorn Security Company, and the baby in her stomach was at a critical point in its development. It couldn’t stop her urges.

Dunn made a detailed plan, a plan that was right, but he made one mistake. If he steeled his resolve to lure Megose behind Chanis Gate, he would’ve stood a chance with the aid of the environment and the items present. If he wanted to wait for backup, he definitely shouldn’t have just taken Saint Selena’s urn out.

Unfortunately, Dunn’s mind wasn’t in the right place due to recent events, and he didn’t think of the most critical point. A diety’s son would be able to feel the threat of the Saint’s urn. Hence, it was triggered and started to absorb its mother’s strength in a bid to be born ahead of time, even though it wasn’t exactly ready.

Azik was in Backlund, but he wasn’t a Planeswalker, so he couldn’t rush back in such short notice.

A few rows were scribbled away.

Megose became a monster, and the fight began. With the aid of the Saint’s urn, Blood Vessel Thief, and two high-level charms that strangely appeared, Megose died and the deity’s son was exorcized. Dunn Smith died as a result, and the power of Saint Selena’s ashes was severely damaged as well. That went perfectly with Ince Zangwill’s intentions.

Ince Zangwill didn’t get a chance to showcase himself, but it didn’t hinder him from achieving his goal.

He killed Klein Moretti, the fellow who kept disrupting his plans, and he took away Saint Selena’s ashes.

Ince Zangwill set up a ritual with the remaining characteristic of Death’s descendant. He consumed Saint Selena’s ashes and successfully advanced from Sequence 5 of the Death Sequence pathway, Gatekeeper, to Sequence 4 of the Evernight Sequence pathway, Nightwatcher. As such, he received godhood characteristics and became a demigod.

The sun continues to shine brilliantly on the land. Nearly no one in Tingen City realized how they narrowly escaped a huge disaster. Monster Ademisaul would be left very confused about it.

The notebook was flipped to the last page. A middle-aged man that was holding onto the book had dark blond hair, a dark blue eye that was nearly black, a tall nose, and tightly pursed lips. His facial features were like that of a statue and didn’t have a single wrinkle. He held a classic quill with his slightly pale hand and wrote a line clearly without dipping into any ink.

He ended with a simple sentence.

Tingen’s story ends here.

The papers rustled as he closed the book, leaving only a brown cover.

Chapter 266:
The World’s Commission

Sequence 0?

There’s still a Sequence 0 above Sequence 1?

Sequence 0 is equivalent to a True God?

There can only be one Sequence 0 per pathway? Is this the true meaning of the paths of the divine?

As long as one consumes the corresponding potion, does a ritual, and grasps the acting method to digest the Beyonder characteristic, an ordinary person can become a god one step at a time?

This is truly blasphemous…

Could the main ingredients of the final potion be the godhood, divine blood, and body of the Eternal Blazing Sun?

†

The information on the diary’s last page was filled with so much information that Klein almost couldn’t think. He almost made additional body movements.

The twenty-two paths of the divine correspond to the twenty-two Sequence 0s… Sequence 0, Sun does sound very powerful… Perhaps, there’s a Sequence 0, Death? I wonder what the names corresponding to the Goddess and the Lord of the Storms are… According to Emperor Roselle’s description, some of these cards are identical to the Major Arcana tarot cards, but some of them are different. The Cards of Blasphemy he created were standardized with the names of the potions… These can no longer be called potions…

Could the reason that the Emperor regretted not choosing the Seer, Apprentice, Marauder pathways be because their corresponding Sequence 0s have yet to appear?

Then what was the reason for the sudden personification of the Hidden Sage who was symbolically a deity?

What was Roselle plotting in the end? It feels like he became the enemy of everyone in the world, and that only seems possible if it was set into motion by that mysterious and ancient organization…

The Primordial Demoness is the name of Sequence 0 for the Demoness pathway?

Klein gradually found his train of thought, and he restrained the turmoil that was going through his mind.

He knew that he couldn’t lose himself in this matter. He had to recover as quickly as possible; otherwise, Justice and The Hanged Man would discover something amiss and find it odd.

Mr. Fool has been reading that page too long!

I really want to obtain one of the Cards of Blasphemy that Emperor Roselle created. I want to know what else there is—other than the godhood-providing potion formulas and the corresponding rituals… Klein suppressed his shock and puzzlement and made Roselle’s diary disappear from his hands.

He rapped the corner of the bronze table and looked to the side.

“Miss Justice, well done. You finished Bakerland in less than a week.

“According to the agreement, what kind of payment do you want?”

Bakerland is dead? That fast? Alger had left the islands in the past few days and hadn’t received the appropriate information. He was astonished for a moment which made Audrey, who was secretly observing him, feel delighted.

Even if Alger was in the in the capital of the Rorsted Archipelago, the City of Generosity, Bayam, he might not have been informed in a timely fashion. After all, cable telegraph could only transmit limited information. Unless it was particularly urgent or important, there was always a delay of a few days. Sometimes, it would even take the colonists of the Rorsted Archipelago a month or two to get an update on the “latest” situation in the Northern Continent.

Restraining his thoughts, The Hanged Man looked at Mr. Fool in the thick fog and respectfully said with a hint of humility, “I’m very sorry. I just managed to contact someone and couldn’t help.”

“This is a commission, not a help request. Don’t worry about it.” Klein chuckled. He turned his gaze back to Miss Justice, waiting for her to say what she wanted in return.

May the Goddess bless me. Please don’t let Miss Justice’s request be too difficult. It’s best if I can repay her with knowledge… I’ve learned quite a lot of amazing things from Roselle’s diary… Klein silently prayed to the Goddess.

Of course, he was very clear that with the gray fog separating them, the Evernight Goddess definitely wouldn’t be able to hear his prayers.

Audrey’s eyes darted around as she thought for a few seconds.

Be honest and not greedy, Audrey, and stick to your principles! She gave a faint smile and said, “No, I’m actually the one still owing you. No—I owe your Blessed the bounty.

“Vice Admiral Qilangos’s bounty was worth a total of 30,000 pounds. I should give your Blessed 15,000 pounds. Killing Bakerland cost 10,000 pounds, so I still need to pay an additional 5000 pounds. However, due to the matter with Bakerland, my finances are recently quite tight. I can only pay this bounty in a few months. Mr. Fool, is that alright?”

After she finished speaking, Audrey quietly exhaled. She felt that the little stone pressing against her heart was finally gone.

Although discussing money and calculating the payment in front of Mr. Fool feels somewhat inappropriate, I can’t hide the rewards I received from his Blessed… Audrey sighed silently.

As for the huge plantation worth more than eight thousand pounds, it was a private form of gratitude from Duke Negan and not a bounty.

5000 pounds? I can get another 5000 pounds? Qilangos’s total bounty actually reached 30,000 pounds! Klein was startled.

Immediately, he fell into an intense mental struggle.

I’m supposed to pay this bounty to Mr. Azik, but I won’t be able to get in touch with him for a long time… Putting the money aside would be a waste… I might as well use this money to enhance myself. When the time comes, I’ll repay him by providing help… Klein made up his mind three seconds later as he lightly nodded at Miss Justice.

“Sure.”

Upon hearing Mr. Fool’s response, Audrey’s graceful seating posture remained the same, but her heart was completely relaxed.

At that moment, Klein leaned back in his chair and fell silent. Then, he manipulated his smurf secretly from a commandeering position.

The World coughed and said, “Can I speak now?”

Audrey looked at Mr. Fool and seeing that he didn’t say a thing, she nodded slightly and said, “Sure.”

At the same time, she once again did a read on the new member, The World, and made a judgment.

When I mentioned that the assassination of Ambassador Bakerland was a result of my commissioning, he didn’t show any shock or surprise. He either doesn’t know the importance of the matter, not understanding the importance of an ambassador, or he’s someone who can keep his calm and is good at hiding his emotions and bodily movements… The way he mouths his words doesn’t match what he says. It should’ve been translated by Mr. Fool as well, which makes it impossible for me to get his original vocal tics, or know what language he usually uses… Thoughts flashed through Audrey’s mind before Mr. World’s hoarse voice sounded.

“I wish to obtain the true root of a Mist Treant, at least 60 milliliters of its juice, as well as the Spring of the Elves Marrow Crystal and the complete spinal fluid of a Dark Patterned Black Panther.

“Which one of you can provide it, or provide any relevant clues?

“What do you wish to exchange them for?”

Klein added the Beyonder ingredient needed by the Apothecary to his commission so that the Tarot Club members wouldn’t be able to guess the main ingredients of the formula he wanted.

Before Justice and The Hanged Man could react, The Sun who had been silent the entire time finally opened his mouth and said, “I know where Mist Treants are and I can help you obtain the materials. However, I must wait until I finish my advancement and have sufficient strength to join the corresponding patrol team.”

Recently, he had been accumulating merit points and rewards. He was working hard to obtain the main ingredients for the Light Suppliant through the City of Silver’s officials and private markets. He was still lacking quite a bit.

As expected of the dangerous City of Silver with its numerous monsters… Klein silently commented in admiration, allowing The World to ask, “Then what do you wish to receive in exchange?”

Without hesitation, Derrick replied, “A weapon that suits me and can increase my combat strength.”

The reason why he didn’t mention the corresponding ingredients for Light Suppliant was because City of Silver had them all. They could be obtained through his own hard work.

Upon hearing this request, Klein immediately thought of the inscribed steel sword that had appeared at the Beyonder gathering organized by the elderly gentleman, Eye of Wisdom.

It was sharp enough, had the effect of exorcism and purification, and could be used for three years. It was valued at 500 pounds, perfectly matching The Sun’s described requirements.

Why didn’t you say so earlier… It has already been bought by someone else… Klein silently stared at the members, while The World nodded and said, “I will find a weapon that meets your requirements as soon as possible. Is this transaction to be witnessed by Mr. Fool?”

Klein nodded slightly to express his agreement.

At that moment, Audrey shot a glance at The Sun and warned him.

“Apart from the Mist Treant’s juice, Mr. World’s requested ingredients correspond to a Sequence 7. The rough price is about 500-700 pounds.”

She felt that The Sun was too naive and was worried that he would be cheated by the unreadable Mr. World with cheap weapons.

Although Mr. Fool is impartial and advocates fair equal exchange, it’s not his place to stop it if both sides agree. After all, some items are of low value but there are people who are in urgent need, so adding a premium to the price is very normal… Audrey thought to herself.

“A Sequence 7 formula is about 800 pounds,” Alger added.

He had an instinctive aversion towards new members.

Klein translated with great difficulty, for he didn’t know what the currency unit of the pound corresponded to in the City of Silver, and could only use a Series 9 potion formula as a unit.

“I understand.” Derrick slightly nodded, and then quietly added, “…Thank you.”

The World maintained his silent and staid temperament and didn’t comment on what had just happened. He turned to Justice and The Hanged Man, waiting for their response.

Audrey thought for a few seconds and said, “Potion formula for Psychiatrist and their corresponding Beyonder ingredients. Uh… That’s Sequence 7 of the Spectator pathway.

“You can gather the information first, and there’s no rush to purchase them. Once I have clues regarding the Dark Patterned Black Panther and Spring of the Elves Marrow Crystal, we can proceed. Uh… if you are willing to exchange it for gold pounds, you can buy it at any time.”

Although I’m out of money recently, I can still raise quite a bit if it’s urgent… Audrey comforted herself.

Alger said in a deep voice, “Potion formula of the Sailor pathway’s Sequence 6 Wind-blessed. This will be more expensive than the Beyonder ingredients that you want—combined.

“If you find it, you can think of the additional payment needed to make up for the difference.

“I can’t guarantee that I’ll be able to help you gather those ingredients. Even if it’s just one of them, you don’t need to expend any resources ahead of time.”

Eh, Mr. Hanged Man should have a close relationship with the Church of Storms… He should be able to get the Wind-blessed formula normally, right? Is he trying to hide the fact that he’s digesting the Seafarer potion quickly? Klein was startled.

“Alright,” The World answered in a low voice and then said, “I have another request.”

Chapter 311:
Observing Each Other

Klein sat in the seat belonging to The Fool and looked around.

“This is Miss Magician, our new member.”

Then, he looked at Fors and introduced the rest to her.

“This is Miss Justice, and that is Mr. Hanged Man…”

As Fors nodded her head as a form of greeting the members with the corresponding code names, she observed the other members.

Miss Justice is blonde and seems very young; she sits with a graceful posture. Mr. Hanged Man has dark blue hair, as messy as seaweeds; he doesn’t have a very bulky figure; he doesn’t like to talk, but when observed by him, it gives me a sense of unease; he must be a leader of some faction… Mr. Sun looks like a teenager; he’s very silent and reserved; other than that, I can’t tell anything else—maybe he’s just as weak as me. Mr. World’s eyes are very cold and quite gloomy; it’s obvious that he isn’t someone to be trifled with… As a writer who had written a best-selling novel, she showcased her unique traits.

While she looked at the other members, they were also looking at her. Among them, Justice Audrey was the most attentive.

From her figure, I can eliminate Miss Xio. Brown hair and slightly curled. Is she Madam Fors? Temporarily, I can’t rule out the possibility that Mr. Fool has pulled in someone else. Hmm, her pronunciation and the way her mouth moves is the same as her Backlund accent. Her aura and emotional colors match as well… It’s unlikely that Mr. Fool will specially create a fake image for the members, right? There’s no need for “Him” to hide anything… After a few seconds of sizing Fors up, Audrey had nearly superimposed the blurry figure with her impression of Fors.

If I can find another trait in other areas, I can almost be certain… She waited with interest to verify her Beyonder powers.

At the same time, she felt that there was no need to reveal her identity to Fors.

It would be better to keep some secrets. Yes… Let’s see when she finds out! Audrey withdrew her gaze, producing a faint smile on her face as she quietly watched from the sidelines.

At that moment, since there were no new Roselle’s diary entries, Klein controlled The World and said, “I want to know about the Devil and Guardian Sequences.”

He was certain that The Sun knew the details of Sequence 6 Devil because he had previously mentioned Devil Studies, and in order to not expose the fact that he was investigating a series of murders, he had deliberately added the Sequence 5 Guardian of the God of Combat pathway—also known as the Giant pathway. It was the mainstream path for Beyonders in the City of Silver, so it was impossible for The Sun to be unaware of it.

As for the corresponding Sequence 9 Warrior, Sequence 8 Pugilist, and Sequence 7 Weapon Master, Klein had long since learned of the details from the Nighthawks’ confidential information. As for information regarding Sequence 6 Dawn Paladin, he had just learned of its information from Bishop Utravsky. Therefore, the only thing that he could ask and be willing to pay a price for without wasting money was Sequence 5 Guardian.

In addition, he didn’t directly ask The Sun, but instead issued this request to everyone, because according to the way things had developed, it was impossible for The World, who had just joined the Tarot Club, to know that the City of Silver held the Giant pathway.

“If it’s just the Devil Sequence, I know a little about it.” Alger, who had some standing in the Church of Storms, interjected.

Derrick Berg glanced at him and without a thought, straightened his back and said, “I’m very knowledgeable about these two Sequences.

“The payment I want is information related to the Fallen Creator.

“The equivalence of the two pieces of information will be determined by Mr. Fool.”

Having said that, he realized that he had not received Mr. Fool’s agreement as he hurriedly turned his head to Mr. Fool to make the request reverently.

Sun, don’t blame me. You were the one who made the request… The corners of Klein’s mouth twitched slightly as he said with a chuckle, “Sure.”

Furthermore, when it comes to the understanding of the True Creator, none of the ladies and gentlemen present can compare to me… he added boldly in his heart.

While they were discussing this matter, The Magician Fors was stunned upon hearing the conversation.

The Devil Sequence is the Devil pathway? Which Sequence number is it?

What is the Guardian pathway? Which Sequence number is it?

I’ve never heard of it…

Fallen Creator? The True Creator?

God, they are actually exchanging information regarding the True Creator!

That deity is known as the most ancient and powerful existence amongst the deities.

What kind of organization did I join?

After receiving a positive reply from The Fool, The World said without any hesitation, “Deal!

“I request a private exchange.”

I really want to hear it… However, I need to be frugal for the time being. There are still two more months until the new year. Endure it, Audrey! Audrey blinked her eyes, reluctantly withdrawing her gaze from The Sun.

Their sights, vision, and spirituality were then shielded by Klein.

The World quickly lowered his head and “wrote” on a conjured sheet of paper his own understanding of the True Creator, including standard likeness such as “The Hanged Giant” and the “Eye behind the Shadow Curtains,” including the information that members of the Aurora Order believed that this evil god was the original creator of everything.

At the end, Klein had included his impression of the evil god through his interaction with the evil god’s spawn, the sensation of the deity’s aura, and the sensation when listening to the True Creator’s voice.

“Fallen, twisted, bloody, crazy, evil.”

Then, as Mr. Fool, he gave a comment, “This piece of information is slightly more valuable than the information regarding the Devil and Guardian Sequences, but the difference isn’t that huge.”

“Thank you, Mr. Fool.” Derrick earnestly received the piece of goatskin and read through it carefully a few times.

The thing he was most concerned about was that the True Creator was known as the creator of everything!

Twisted, fallen, crazy… Derrick repeated the words, vaguely able to see the dark tragedy that had engulfed everyone in the City of Silver for more than two thousand years.

Did the Lord not abandon us? It’s just that “He” had gone mad… Derrick found himself able to resist using blasphemous thoughts to examine the Lord that created everything, the omnipotent and omniscient God who was worshipped by the City of Silver.

“It’s time for you to answer my question,” The World urged in a hoarse voice.

Derrick restrained his seething and sorrowful thoughts and said after two seconds of silence, “When different species of creatures consume the Devil potion, they will experience different types of mutation. They will have traits that are unique to them. Which kind of Devil would you like to know about?”

There are actually distinctions? Klein was puzzled.

He soon realized one thing—there was a blind spot in his thought process!

What if the serial killer wasn’t a human but an animal?

After consuming the corresponding potion, it could transform into a Devil animal!

Step by step, one Sequence at a time, it will turn into a Devil!

Although the probability of an animal losing control far exceeds that of a human’s, it was still not enough to deal with “what ifs”… I have to investigate this… But in that case, there would be more questions. Where did the Devil, mutated from an animal, obtain the potion and Beyonder ingredients? It should be impossible for it to join Beyonder circles… Klein maintained his silence and manipulated The World to say, “What I want to know is the common trait of all kinds of Devils.”

Derrick recollected and organized his knowledge before saying, “The most frightening thing about a Devil is that if you can cause lethal damage to it in a very short period of time and take action to put that into practice, then he can sense, notice, and grasp where the danger comes from and who it came from, and then selectively kill or seek revenge on them.

“And this period of time varies from a few minutes to a day. Different Devils have different instincts.”

This ability is a little scary… However, it’s different from a Clown’s intuition. It doesn’t seem like it can be used in combat but instead, detect the source of the danger ahead of time. It’s closer to the “Whim[32]” ability I’ve read in xianxia novels in my previous life… I don’t know if I can interfere with or even block this intuition in this mysterious space above the gray fog. Would Stuart end up in danger… Klein leaned back into his chair, seemingly uninterested in the subject of the discussion between The Sun and The World.

Seeing that The World didn’t show any signs of surprise, Derrick continued, “They all possess the ability to gigantify their bodies and thus break free from their bindings, temporarily increasing their strength and speed; their skin is mutable, equivalent to wearing a layer of hard armor; their blood and flesh can act as a retardant and reduce damage; they’re immune to most toxins and do not fear curses or flames to a certain degree; they have innate flame and corruption-type spells; they’re cold-blooded, don’t panic, don’t feel fear, and have a strong ability when it comes to physical combat; they’re also adept at using various items to inflict damage.

“Their greatest weakness is that they tend to lose control. Even if they don’t, they will often display a cold-blooded and cruel madness, being easily controlled by desires such as bloodlust and murderous intent.”

Really strong, as expected of a Sequence 6 Devil. Could it be that among the 22 Beyonder paths below the High Sequences, Sequence 6 or Sequence 7 are the thresholds of a qualitative change? In this respect, different Sequences differ, thus they have become the dividing lines between ancient and modern Mid-Sequences… Klein controlled The World and said, “I’m very satisfied with your information.”

Derrick didn’t act modestly. He nodded and said, “Guardians seldom suffer damage. Once they enter a defensive state and give up attacking, few can break through their defenses below that of the High-Sequences. It’s the same for numerous types of damage. When they attack, their corresponding defense will decrease significantly, but it will still be stronger than full-body armor.

“Their Sword of Dawn and their Hurricane of Light, as well as their other Beyonder powers, allow them to deal damage to any type of monsters.

“They’re not confused by illusions. They can help their comrades within a certain range by taking damage and protecting them.”

†

Following the descriptions given by Derrick, Klein couldn’t help but sigh in his heart.

Compared to a Guardian, a Dawn Paladin’s defense is like that of a child versus an adult. A Guardian would probably be able to withstand the bullets of a steam rifle… In the wars of this era, they wouldn’t die unless they were focused on by large-caliber cannons.

Chapter 570:
Not Admitting or Denying

Eh, why is she looking at Mr. Fool… Audrey sharply noticed The Hermit’s subtle motion. This left her somewhat suspicious.

From her point of view, this was an atypical response. Mr. Hanged Man was clearly mentioning something that had little to do with everyone. He was talking about the so-called Sea God Kalvetua’s ability to occasionally reply to its believers despite its apparent death, so why would Ma’am Hermit look towards Mr. Fool?

Kalvetua’s death… Occasionally replying to its believers… Ma’am Hermit is looking at Mr. Fool… Could it be… Audrey’s eyes lit up as she came to a conclusion.

Could it be that Mr. Fool is the one replying to Kalvetua’s believers?

Ma’am Hermit knows about this, so?

As thoughts whizzed through her mind, Audrey had turned her body halfway to look expectantly at Mr. Fool, who was seated leisurely at the end of the long bronze table.

Meanwhile, Alger was also surprised and alarmed about The Hermit’s unexpected reaction.

I was only trying to sound her out about what connection she has with the Moses Ascetic Order member, Leticia. Why would she suddenly turn to look at Mr. Fool?

Could it be that she knows that the current “Sea God” is a manifestation of Mr. Fool?

Her reaction implies this is highly likely!

Before she was recruited into the Tarot Club, did she have a lot of secret exchanges with Mr. Fool, and was already secretly working for him?

The more Alger thought, the more he paid attention to The Hermit. Then, he subconsciously joined her in looking towards Mr. Fool, who was shrouded in the grayish-white fog.

He, The Hermit, and Justice turned around at different times, but their nearly unanimous actions made The Magician Fors and company notice something amiss.

Why are they looking at Mr. Fool? Does Sea God Kalvetua’s death have to do with Mr. Fool? Believing they were smart, Fors and Emlyn began guessing at the reason as they cast their gaze to the end of the long bronze table.

Derrick didn’t know who Sea God Kalvetua was, nor did he understand what it meant for it to respond to its believers even after its death. However, since everyone was looking at Mr. Fool, he naturally looked over as well.

The World was late by a second, as though he was deliberating over something.

He first scanned The Hanged Man, making him shudder in fear. Then, he changed the direction of his gaze.

At this point, Klein had already come to realize which detail Ma’am Hermit had used to guess that he was the one replying to Sea God Kalvetua’s believers in its stead. He was still stumped over what stance to use.

Should I pretend that it’s a trivial matter and that I didn’t take it to heart, but since you mentioned it, I’ll just admit it in passing? Or should I take the stance that since I’m a god, there’s no need for me to explain myself to you, so there’s no need for me to admit or deny anything… Klein recalled The Fool’s persona and quickly made a decision.

The choice was to neither admit or deny anything, so as to prevent him from losing his standing as a god. However, he would add a single sentence on a particular point, making those who had failed to guess it become more puzzled, while the suspicious ones would be enlightened but would still be left shrouded in confusion as they realized, deep down, how unfathomable Mr. Fool was.

With this in mind, Klein, who had leaned back, chuckled. He said leisurely and indifferently, “Kalvetua became a demigod by relying on a relic left behind by Calamity Cohinem.”

So they’re consulting Mr. Fool about the situation with the “Sea God”… But that doesn’t convince me. It feels like there’s a deeper truth hidden behind this matter… Could it be… No way, right? Fors frowned as she began coming up with all sorts of thoughts.

As expected! Cattleya believed Mr. Fool was giving a straightforward answer while also informing them of some secrets.

That demigod scepter is Kalvetua’s characteristic or Calamity Cohinem’s relic, or is it something that covers both definitions? Who is Calamity Cohinem? The name sounds elven. Yes, The Hanged Man mentioned that Leticia found an ancient elven ruin… It’s the residence of a high elf?

How did Mr. Fool get that scepter? Did he rely on The Hanged Man or someone else? No, it doesn’t seem like The Hanged Man; otherwise, he wouldn’t have proactively mentioned this matter… What motive does Mr. Fool have behind responding to the Sea God’s believers? Is this required for “His” awakening, something that can truly affect reality?

The more Cattleya thought, the more she found Mr. Fool unfathomable. It was just like how “His” body was being concealed by the thick gray fog. The clearer she could see him, the more puzzled, horrified, and apprehensive she became.

This might be a tussle between gods… Cattleya sighed inwardly as the emotions got the better of her.

I guessed right! Alger finally verified that the present “Sea God” was a manifestation of The Fool. His worries and indecision from before were instantly rewarded.

On certain occasions, as a fake Sea God believer, I can openly pray… I wonder how much Mr. Fool has recovered. How much of his power can he release from the seal? It’s at least at the demigod level. He will be able to provide tremendous protection at sea…

The Hermit’s unsurprised reaction implies that she had long interacted with Mr. Fool and had learned of certain things ahead of time. This implies that her Sequence isn’t low. She might really be a powerhouse at the pirate admiral level… This is both good and bad news for me.

The good news is that I have an additional powerful faction at sea supporting me. At times, we can tacitly cooperate and complete matters that were previously deemed unimaginable. The bad news is that a lot of my news and resource channels will be overshadowed by hers. My purpose in the Tarot Club will drastically decline. Of course, that’s under the premise that she really is Admiral of Stars.

Yes, I have to adjust my focus from gathering news and resources and align it towards the Church. This is something she can’t supplant me, Alger thought with joy and wariness.

That Sea God is really Mr. Fool! No, no, no, it should be said that the present Sea God is Mr. Fool’s manifestation! “He” has truly begun interfering with the real world? This is great! In the future, I can pray to Sea God directly and receive a response when I’m out traveling at sea? Audrey felt surprised, overjoyed, and proud.

According to what she knew, the Churches didn’t do fixed ritualistic magic internally. The ones who received responses by solely praying to the deities were mainly priests or a chance occurrence; otherwise, they were only a handful of Blessed.

As for receiving a response from every prayer, they would be an extreme exception, even among Blessed.

But I can! Mr. Fool is returning to his throne, one step at a time. Replacing Sea God is one of those steps… Audrey didn’t hide the changes in her emotions as she smiled, sitting straight and elegantly.

Cohinem? That’s an elf’s name. I think I’ve heard someone mention it before… Emlyn attempted to recall, but it was in vain.

As for Kalvetua’s death and how the “Sea God” still replied to its believers, as well as the reason why The Hermit, Justice, The Hanged Man had looked towards Mr. Fool, he had made a slight guess without thinking too deeply about the matter.

What has this got to do with me? It doesn’t affect my saving of the Sanguine, nor is it anything of interest! Anyway, I can just pray to Mr. Fool if there are any problems! Emlyn mumbled to himself, showing disdain towards the emotional changes the others had.

Calamity? Queen of Calamity? But there are no records that say that her name is Cohinem… Derrick turned his head to the left very slightly, a common tick he did when he recalled things.

From the looks of it, Little Sun isn’t sure if Cohinem is the Queen of Calamity; otherwise, he wouldn’t have such a reaction… Klein retracted his gaze in disappointment.

He controlled The World to cough, pulling everyone back from their thoughts.

Following that, The World conjured a picture with The Fool’s help. He showed it to both sides of the table and asked, “Does anyone know her?”

It was a picture of the red-haired Helene. Klein mainly wanted to know if Admiral of Stars Cattleya or The Hanged Man Alger knew her. After all, they were well-informed people out at sea.

Alger glanced at it and just as he was about to say that he didn’t know her, he heard Ma’am Hermit say with a deep voice, “Red-haired Helene. She’s from a fallen noble family and has the bloodline from the Intis’s Sauron family.”

Cattleya paused before adding, “She was once a trader out at sea, but she was later said to have been abducted by Ailment Maiden Tracy.”

Abducted by Vice Admiral Ailment Tracy? I thought it would be some contrived story about a domineering pirate and a noble lady… However, Tracy can be considered a domineering pirate. Heh heh… Klein instantly made some connections.

Fors was still lost in her thoughts over the connection between Sea God and The Fool when she suddenly snapped to her senses. She acutely noticed that great opportunities lay in red-haired Helene and Vice Admiral Ailment’s story as she began to daydream.

To her regret, Ma’am Hermit had only said a few sentences without continuing.

The Hermit knows Vice Admiral Ailment… However, that doesn’t imply anything. Beyonders of a certain Sequence or knowledgeable people will know who the seven pirate admirals are. Their bounty posters are everywhere… Hmm, The Hermit is rather aware of matters over at Intis. This is something that can be determined for now… The Hanged Man wasn’t interested in red-haired Helene, only The Hermit’s real identity.

With red-haired Helene’s matter coming to a close, Audrey began considering if she should consult the others about the mind dragon.

Unlike before, there was now the addition of Ma’am Hermit, who was of unknown character and dubious allegiances. This left her hesitant.

After a brief deliberation, she said, “I recently sought out the traces of a mind dragon and went to a place which has the tradition of worshiping dragons.”

She had concealed the exact location as the details might implicate her.

Chapter 800:
Psychologically Becoming “Better”

Who is it? Who is the one speaking? Klein’s muscles tensed up as he nearly opened his eyes.

At that moment, his back oozed with sweat that soaked his shirt.

What he was most alarmed of wasn’t the words said, but that it directly sounded in his heart and had modulated the voice to sound exactly like his.

Although I maintained my lucidity in that dream, I still had my Spirit Body tainted by his psyche that was on the verge of losing control? Or is someone using that Keeper to pass me a message? Countless guesses ran through Klein’s mind. Finally, combining the contents of what was said and his own situation, he came up with a preliminary judgment.

The number of people who knows about my identity as Klein Moretti is few to begin with. Likewise for those who know that Klein Moretti had once sworn an oath while touching a Holy Artifact. Furthermore, there’s almost no intersection between the two.

Mr. Azik had heard me mention the former matter before, but if he wants to give me any reminders, he can directly do it through a messenger. There’s no need to use such a frightening method… Will Auceptin might know; after all, he’s a Snake of Mercury who represents fate. But by the same logic, “He” can directly contact me… Of course, I can eliminate the possibility that he suddenly had the thought of frightening me. I just thought in the afternoon about having a chance of becoming his godfather…

The Antigonus family’s notebook had corrupted the Keeper, just like how it used the Misfortune Cloth Puppet to deliver the symbol? But if it really is the Antigonus family’s notebook, why didn’t it just give me the potion formula directly? Or try negotiating with me to help in a Notebook Jailbreak… Saint Samuel Cathedral is the headquarters of the Backlund diocese, making it at a higher level than Saint Selena Cathedral. That notebook shouldn’t have the ability to do anything further. It should be securely sealed…

Apart from them, there is only one entity who is aware of both matters—the Evernight Goddess. However, with a deity’s pride, “She” has no need to pretend to act as a passerby to call me out with a polite and estranged tone… I’m in Saint Samuel Cathedral, so all “She” needs to do is produce a revelation, and dozens of Beyonders will appear to mow me down. And as a diocese headquarters, with sufficient preparation, they can probably disrupt Traveling; therefore, there’s no need to go through so much trouble…

Hmm, there’s still one more person who’s aware of both matters…

That’s myself!

Before planning my operation, I’ve actually considered the corresponding problem. Back then, my conclusion was that I didn’t need to worry too much about it because only after advancing to Faceless will some of the gray fog’s powers enter the real world, allowing certain demigods to sense my uniqueness. Before this, only Beyonders from the Monster pathway could discover a tiny bit of my uniqueness, and back when I touched the holy sword and made that oath, I had yet to become a Clown…

Just because of the secret connection established from the oath, it made the Goddess slowly sense something about me. It’s been so long, and I haven’t seen “Her” take any action… That female Angel, hmm… she should be an angel. She had even smiled at me when she wiped away Mr. A… Therefore, the Goddess might be happy to see me take away the Antigonus family’s notebook. Although I’m not sure of “Her” motives, I can only accept it and subsequently think of ways to deal with it at my current level. This is ultimately safer than climbing the main peak of the Hornacis mountain range… Of course, that’s built on the premise that the lady which wiped away Mr. A is an angel of the Church…

Hmm… Although I had undergone all kinds of acting during the Faceless stage and got to know myself well, I’ve consumed additional potions without completely digesting them. And Marionettist requires every marionette to adhere to a specific persona. This also easily causes a personality dissociation… Also, to steal the Antigonus family’s notebook and to act as Dwayne Dantès, I’m under immense stress. I am subconsciously wavering and am suspicious… In this state, the Keeper’s corrupted psyche of nearly losing control had agitated my Spirit Body, causing me to have a split personality?

Just as Klein thought of this, the familiar yet unfamiliar voice resounded in his mind again.

“Heh, your considerations are too idealized. All of your actions are fundamentally all thanks to luck. If that high-ranking deacon, Crestet Cesimir, with the holy sword was here in Backlund to handle Beyonder cases, can you guarantee that the holy sword wouldn’t sense you when you are in the same cathedral? Both of you are linked by an oath!”

If Deacon Cesimir were to come, I’ll abandon this plan… Besides, it’s also not possible to avoid it ahead of time. I’ll find an excuse or reason to be out of town for some time… Klein mumbled inwardly.

Then, he heard the voice belonging to himself sound in his mind:

“This makes it a situation prone to too many accidents and unpredictable developments.

“Before coming to the cathedral, didn’t you also not consider that the mere observation of Spirit Body Threads would result in a mutation?”

My nervousness back then was the anxiety that something happened beyond my expectations. However, as it’s a mere observation without me making any direct contact, I didn’t believe that there would be too great a problem. I should be more cautious in the future… Also, accidents and developments exist for everything… Who exactly are you? Klein closed his eyes as he pretended to focus on praying.

The voice hesitated and said, “I’m Klein. You are Zhou Mingrui.

“No, I’m Zhou Mingrui. You are Klein…”

Indeed… Klein felt his hair stand on end once again. He decided to leave Saint Samuel Cathedral immediately, return home, and resolve the problem of his character dissociation.

When the symptoms first appear, the situation is easier to resolve. Once the other personality stabilizes and becomes stronger, it will begin to snatch control of the body. I might even need external help when that happens!

He opened his eyes and looked at Elektra with a tranquil expression.

“I feel like I’ve calmed down.”

Ever since I got a mental illness, my mind is a lot better… As he spoke, Klein inwardly gave a self-deprecating comment.

He enjoyed lampooning, partially because it was in his character to do so, and partially to enforce his personality. It was ultimately to remind himself who he was, so as not to lose himself to his acting.

Bishop Elektra smiled.

“May the Goddess bless you.”

As he spoke, he took a cup of water from a priest’s hand and passed it to Dwayne Dantès.

Without any explanation needed, Klein knew that it was holy water. He often drank it in the past; hence, hiding his anxiety, he received it in a composed manner and downed it.

A refreshing feeling slushed down his throat, jolting his mind as he became a lot more awake. Even the voice in his mind weakened.

This has the effect of placating the Spirit Body… The Church does view Dwayne Dantès with great importance. Of course, this is created by their Beyonders… As Klein nodded at Bishop Elektra, he drew the sign of the crimson moon and staidly walked to the altar and donated fifty pounds into the donation box.

After doing everything, he led Richardson and left the cathedral, riding the carriage back to Böklund Street.

On his trip back, he didn’t feed the pigeons, because an ordinary person who had just encountered something would hardly have the peace of mind to do so.

After returning home, the silent Klein used the excuse of an afternoon nap to dismiss his servants. In his master bedroom’s bathroom, he took four steps counterclockwise and headed above the gray fog.

Passing through the roars and ravings, he didn’t feel his body be purified. He was increasingly certain that the voice in his mind originated from himself. It was a result of being corrupted and agitated, causing a character dissociation.

Sitting in the high-back chair of The Fool, Klein immediately studied his Spirit Body’s situation. He discovered that there were some signs of chaos without it being pure. The corresponding aura colors were somewhat spotted.

After seriously contemplating for two minutes and ignoring the echoing noise in his head, Klein conjured The World Gehrman Sparrow and made him devoutly pray:

“Honorable Mr. Fool… Please inform The Moon that I wish to rent the Mental Terror Candle for half a day. I know he has the means of obtaining it…”

Very early on, his identity as The World had been prepared for Sherlock Moriarty, so Klein wasn’t worried about it.

†

South of the Bridge, Harvest Church.

Emlyn White, who was anticipating his obtaining of Lilith’s Ring in the evening, suddenly saw the endless gray fog and heard The World.

Alarmed, he muttered in silence, How does he know that I can get the Mental Terror Candle?

Chapter 1118:
Klein’s Fear

In the past, Rose Redemption could be called the Deity Alliance… But such an organization could only develop itself quietly under the might of the Ancient Sun God. It had to hide, hide, hide, and secretly scheme in the palace of dusk… How powerful was the Ancient Sun God in the past… Klein couldn’t help but let out a breath as he felt deeply poignant.

He examined his own Tarot Club and realized that, compared to the Rose Redemption, it was like child’s play. Even if he counted the auxiliary members, Will Auceptin, Pallez Zoroast, Azik Eggers, and Reinette Tinekerr, there was no way to compare with the Rose Redemption at its peak.

No, even if I compare it with the current watered-down version of Rose Redemption, there’s still a huge gap between it and the Tarot Club. After all, its leader and convener is only a Sequence 4 saint… Klein gave a self-deprecating laugh as he turned his attention to the eleven figures.

Based on their images, titles, and true names, I can confirm that the Wind Angel, Wisdom Angel, and White Angel are the current Lord of Storms, the God of Knowledge and Wisdom, and the Eternal Blazing Sun. “They” really betrayed the Ancient Sun God, the City of Silver’s Creator, and “They” even feasted on the deity “They” served… The God of Combat and Earth Mother are indeed survivors of the Giant King’s Court. One of them is the eldest son of the Giant King, and the other is “His” queen. They’re mother and son, so that way, the fact that Feynapotter didn’t directly declare war on the Lord of Storms to help Feysac makes things a little odd. It requires some thought…

Also, the Goddess was indeed a former subsidiary god of the Annihilation Demonic Wolf, the Goddess of Misfortune, Amanises. After that ancient god perished, not only did “She” grasp the authority of the Evernight and successfully ascend to the throne of Sequence 0, she also single-handedly destroyed all the descendants of Flegrea, sealed the Antigonus family’s angel within the Nation of the Evernight, and used the Mother of the Sky’s body as “Her” vessel for a descent… That’s ruthless…

As a Blessed of Evernight, Klein subconsciously raised his head to look around when he thought of this, afraid that his inner thoughts would leak out to the outside world.

After entering the foggy town and learning that Antigonus and the Mother of the Sky were the descendants of the ancient god, Flegrea, Klein had a certain idea as to the true identity of the Evernight Goddess. After all, in the history of the City of Silver, it clearly stated that the Annihilation Demonic Wolf controlled the authority of the Evernight and had many strange powers.

Combined with the Antigonus family’s possession of the Seer pathway, and the Mother of the Sky of the Nation of the Night clearly belonging to Evernight, Klein suspected that the Annihilation Demonic Wolf Flegrea was an ancient god that had mixed two non-neighboring pathways’ Beyonder characteristics. Therefore, “He” was extremely crazy and almost irrational. “His” goal was to destroy and corrupt everything.

Hence, he guessed that the Evernight Goddess might have something to do with the ancient god, Flegrea. From Groselle’s Travels, he learned that one of the two subsidiary gods of the Demonic Wolf King had gone missing after “He” perished, while the other had submitted to the Phoenix Ancestor. Furthermore, that true name corresponded to Death of the Fourth Epoch, Mr. Azik’s father. With that, he could vaguely connect the Goddess of Misfortune Amanises to the Evernight Goddess.

However, due to his temporary status as a Blessed of Evernight, he didn’t dare think too much about it. Instead, he focused his attention elsewhere.

At this moment, when he saw “Her” real name, he wasn’t too shocked. Instead, he felt relieved and felt as though he were on firm ground. In addition, he was even more fearful of the Evernight Goddess.

Because “She” didn’t want the ancient god, Flegrea, to be revived, the Goddess controlled the various matters of the Seer pathway, preventing Beyonders who aren’t cleared by “Her” to advance further?

That’s right, that ecclesiastic in Afternoon Town mentioned who tempted Dark Angel Sasrir, the left hand of God, and the deputy of the divine kingdom, but he couldn’t say the name, as if it had been “erased.” Isn’t this a demonstration of “Concealment” powers?

Other than a place like the Giant King’s Court, there’s no way to say the names “Evernight Goddess” and “Amanises” together. Even if one did, no one would be able to hear it…

There are two people who convened Rose Redemption, one is Dark Angel Sasrir, and the other is the Goddess…

Apart from the venue where the ploy was conceived, it’s filled with the forces of Concealment…

In other words, the Goddess had single-handedly directed the fall of the Ancient Sun God, started the Cataclysm, and ended the Third Epoch…

Compared to “Her,” be it Adam or Amon, they are still far from “Her”…

How could such a true deity be so easily trapped by Adam’s arrangements and be unable to interfere with matters of the real world?

Although it’s not a conspiracy where something the Goddess yearns for the most is used, making “Her” willingly walk into a trap, how can the Goddess, who wields the powers of Concealment and plotted the death of the City of Silver Creator, be unprepared?

Also, what does “This is also in line with ‘His’ thoughts” mean? Who does “He” refer to?

Uh, after understanding so much hidden history, will I digest the Scholar of Yore potion on the spot once I drink it…

With this in mind, Klein raised his right hand and rubbed his temples, forcing himself to focus his thoughts elsewhere.

When that ecclesiastic phantom mentioned the fourth King of Angels, it self-destructed. Was it because the remaining three became true gods?

However, the residents of the City of Silver would occasionally use the names Badheil and Herabergen, so why wasn’t there an anomaly?

What is the difference?

The strongest among the Kings of Angels, the left hand of God, Sasrir—why did “He” disappear into the rivers of history? Uh, perhaps “He” is one of the present-day evil gods, the True Creator, the Dark Side of the Universe, or the Mother Tree of Desire?

There are remnants of the godhood of degeneracy outside the hall. Was this left behind by “Him”?

Yes, the birth of the True Creator is related to the Rose Redemption. How will “He” react when “He” sees the murals in this hall?

With a thought, Klein cast his gaze at Shepherd Elder Lovia.

The lady looked a little lost. She didn’t seem to understand the titles and names, but she recognized a portion of them. For example, Angel of Fate Ouroboros.

She had become a believer of the True Creator in the temple ruins filled with murals that were left behind by Ouroboros.

Derrick also stole a glance at Elder Lovia, but he didn’t notice any obvious changes in her emotions.

As The Sun of the Tarot Club, Derrick was one of the people present who knew the situation of the outside world the most. Furthermore, he had long known who the Kings of Angels were. He suspected that three of them had later become deities. At this moment, he was the least confused and perplexed. He was only slightly shocked at Rose Redemption’s level.

This was more exaggerated than he had imagined!

It’s no wonder the Lord perished… Derrick was first enlightened before he felt his heart turn heavy.

At this moment, he swept his gaze and saw the Chief’s face turn pale and ugly. He even muttered a few words softly, “This is impossible, impossible…”

…As far as I can remember, the Chief has never lost his composure like this… Did he think of the Lord perishing due to Rose Redemption? He can’t accept that “He” will never return? However, he had long learned of this from me… Just as Derrick was feeling puzzled, he discovered that, aside from his tightly pursed lips, the Chief’s expression had returned to normal.

In the minds of the other members of the exploration team, the prophecy they had previously learned in Afternoon Town appeared:

“Omnipotent Lord, I repent. … tempted Sasrir. The Kings often came to the palace belonging to the dusk to conspire.

“It was already too late by the time I discovered all of this. Degeneration, bloodshed, darkness, rot, murders, corruption, and shadows had already drowned this piece of land.

“A huge calamity will begin here!”

Haim, who was holding the Unshadowed Crucifix, took a long while to calm his emotions. He said in a slightly hoarse voice, “This is the place belonging to the dusk. These are the subsidiary gods and Kings of Angels of the Second Epoch?

“They plotted everything, causing a huge calamity to happen. They made the Lord forsake this land?”

Colin Iliad pulled out the two swords in front of him and half-turned around, calmly replying, “Most likely.”

“If we can figure out what exactly happened back then, do we have a chance to please the Lord and let ‘Him’ look at this land again?” Upon hearing the Chief’s answer, Antiona asked anxiously.

At that moment, Derrick seemed to see a trace of pity and sadness in the Chief’s eyes. He heard him acknowledge and say, “Perhaps.”

“Then let’s continue exploring!” The other team members pleaded with burning eyes.

This was the closest the City of Silver had gotten to having a glimmer of hope over the past two to three thousand years. None of them wished to let it go, even if they had to sacrifice their lives for it.

Colin Iliad slowly surveyed the area and said, “Don’t forget the principles to uphold during explorations. Don’t act rashly at any time.

“Having confirmed that this place is related to redemption, we can always come a second time, a third time, or even more. There’s no need to be so impatient.”

Upon hearing his words, the other members of the exploration team calmed down. They replied one after another, “Yes, Your Excellency.”

Under the arrangements of Demon Hunter Colin, the remaining members split up into small groups and carefully searched the hall. They didn’t discover anything else that was valuable beyond the murals.

Of course, it wasn’t that there was no such thing. This was, after all, a divine kingdom of an ancient god. What seemed like an ordinary long table, chairs, stone pillars, and torches might have special effects when taken outside. Furthermore, those effects could last for a very long period of time. Alas, it wasn’t convenient for the City of Silver’s expedition team to bring them around, as they lacked practical value.

As for the other murals, they were profiled from different angles of the main murals. When combined, they formed a three-dimensional scene.

After completing the search, Derrick and company gathered again and followed the Chief to the exit at the back of the hall.

There was a gray-blue door with a single pane.

With a ten-meter-tall door between the two of them, Colin Iliad carefully observed for a while before finally saying, “There’s a powerful guard outside.”

Chapter 1392:
Yesterday No More

In a room beside the Evernight cathedral in the Southern Continent, East Balam, Leonard’s consciousness returned to the real world.

After a few seconds of silence, he picked up the cup of coffee that had turned cold and took a sip.

The bitter taste filled his mouth, gradually waking his mind up.

“Old Man, what happened today?” Finally, Leonard couldn’t help but ask.

After a moment of silence, Pallez Zoroast replied wistfully, “Error has perished.”

Error… Leonard almost didn’t realize which existence Old Man was referring to.

In the next second, he couldn’t hide his astonishment as he nearly forgot to whisper, “Amon?”

This was a standard true god!

“Yes.” Pallez Zoroast’s voice sounded like “He” had aged considerably. “To be precise, Amon’s main body perished.”

Leonard wasn’t in the mood to distinguish the subtle meaning behind Old Man’s words. He asked in disbelief, “Wh-Why was there no sign of it?”

He had witnessed the phenomena before and after the God of Combat died. He knew that it was a change that would affect the entire world and bring about many terrifying monsters and dangerous regions.

And just now, the only two abnormalities were:

The doors and windows suddenly closing, and him seemingly forgetting something.

In reality, the latter wasn’t strange at all. Most people would encounter something similar during their daily lives.

Pallez Zoroast’s tone sank.

“‘He’ should’ve perished in Sefirah Castle.”

Sefirah Castle? Leonard was shocked.

The venue of the gathering he had just attended was inside Sefirah Castle!

A war between gods has just erupted there? Amon actually infiltrated Sefirah Castle? Amidst Leonard’s thoughts, his expression gradually turned solemn.

“Old Man, Mr. Fool was injured because of this and had no choice but to enter a state of slumber?”

“Is ‘He’ about to enter a state of slumber?” Pallez Zoroast asked in return.

“He” didn’t seem to be too surprised about this.

Leonard tersely acknowledged.

“The reason ‘He’ summoned us today was because of this matter.”

Pallez Zoroast fell silent for a few seconds before saying,

“‘His’ choice to enter a state of slumber is indeed related to the previous battle of gods and Amon’s infiltration, but it’s not because of injuries, but because of corruption.”

“Corruption?” Leonard blurted out in surprise.

Even at Mr. Fool’s level, irreversible corruption can still be encountered by “Him?”

Pallez Zoroast regained “His” previous poignant tone:

“Everything has godhood. By relying on godhood to become a powerhouse, one can never escape the shackles of godhood.

“On this point, it’s the same for you and me. Likewise for The Fool. Heh, perhaps ‘He’ shouldn’t be called ‘The Fool’ anymore. ‘He’ is equivalent to half a ‘Lord of Mysteries.’”

Lord of Mysteries… Regarding the problem of the mental imprint in a Beyonder characteristic, Leonard indeed had a deeper understanding of it than demigods at his level. However, he still had several holes in the knowledge on this matter. Even though he had heard Old Man mention the term “Lord of Mysteries,” he didn’t understand what it meant.

However, at present, he could confirm that Mr. Fool’s level had transcended Sequence 0 according to Mr. Fool’s words during the gathering, and what Old Man had just said, “His” strength was enough to kill a true god.

Leonard cleverly didn’t probe further. He changed the topic in a deep voice:

“Old Man, why is Klein sleeping as well?

“Are you able to wake him up as soon as possible?”

Pallez Zoroast’s tone was somewhat odd.

“How could an old and weak angel like me know about matters at the level of gods?

“As for the awakening, even The Fool has no better solution, much less me?”

Leonard remained silent for a moment. He picked up his coffee cup and took another sip.

After a while, he asked hesitantly, “Old Man, do you have any way of ‘Stealing’ the artistic flair of others?”

Pallez Zoroast scoffed.

“The definition of artistic flair is vague with no clear categorization. There’s no way to ‘Steal’ it.

“However, if you change it to natural talent, there’s a way.”

“…Forget it.” Leonard ultimately couldn’t do anything about “Stealing” the natural talent of others to help him resolve his problem.

Pallez Zoroast added with a smile, “If you can’t accept this method, then you can find a natural talent that you want of someone who’s very poor. Make a deal with him and give him the money he wants to exchange for the corresponding natural talent.”

“It’s a little like a deal with the devil…” Leonard commented objectively.

Pallez Zoroast chuckled and said, “There’s another simple solution. That is to spend money to hire naturally talented people to help you resolve the corresponding problems.”

“…Old Man, why didn’t you say so earlier?” Leonard instantly saw hope.

Pallez Zoroast scoffed.

“You didn’t manage to think of something that simple?

“I thought you had eliminated this option before consulting me.”

Leonard ignored Old Man’s mockery. After some serious thought, he felt that this idea was indeed feasible.

However, he soon felt a little guilty and uneasy, as if he was avoiding his responsibility.

Regarding this matter, I still have to do something personally… Apart from inviting someone to write songs and poems, I have to write a little… With this in mind, Leonard suddenly stood up and walked to the door.

“Where are you going?” Pallez Zoroast asked in surprise.

Leonard frowned slightly as he said firmly, “I’m going to the nearby bookstore to buy some poem anthologies.”

Ever since he advanced to Nightmare, he had given up the collection of poems he had bought in the past, making most of them nothing but decorations. When he became a Spirit Warlock, he began to collect poem anthologies that were suitable for some spirits to read, allowing him to chant the appropriate parts in a battle to create Beyonder effects that worked in concert with him.

Therefore, when he came to the Southern Continent, he didn’t bring a single poem anthology book. He only remembered a few of those that he often used in the past.

I never expected that, after becoming a high-ranking deacon, I would need to read poem anthologies again… Leonard sighed inwardly as his steps became firmer.

Pallez Zoroast had never imagined that Leonard’s next step would be to buy poem anthologies. After a while, “He” probed, “Is this an order from The Fool?”

“Yes, for promoting the corresponding legendary stories,” Leonard answered simply as he opened the door and walked out.

Pallez Zoroast fell silent once again before saying, “Apart from writing poems, you have to pay more attention to the besiegement of the Rose School of Thought.”

Leonard walked down the stairs and entered the streets. He looked at the pedestrians and nodded gently.

“Yes.”

At that moment, as he walked towards the bookstore, he felt as though he had returned to Tingen, back to the time when he was still a Midnight Poet. At that time, he had also walked along the bustling streets, preparing to buy a copy of “Classical Poems Anthology of the Loen Kingdom” and “Selected Poems of Roselle.”

†

Backlund, at the Harvest Church south of the Bridge.

After Emlyn White regained his senses, he found himself standing in front of a window.

The sun was already dim outside, and the flowers were flourishing.

His feelings towards Mr. Fool’s slumber were slightly different from the other Tarot Club members.

Other than heaviness, poignancy, sadness, and confusion, there was also the confidence that things would end well.

Internally within the Sanguine, some of the Marquises and Earls were rather old. Even though they lived longer than most demigods at the same level, they were still in advanced stages of their lives. At this time, they often chose to sleep and use similar methods to extend their lifespans. The effects were pretty good.

Therefore, Emlyn had long been accustomed to matters regarding slumbers. He knew that it wasn’t equivalent to passing away, nor was it equivalent to perishing. He believed that if the correct solution was found, Mr. Fool would have a high chance of waking up.

He looked out the window and muttered to himself, “Mr. Fool has entered a state of slumber, and the Ancestor’s revelation is often interfered with. It’s obvious that ‘She’ can’t provide help frequently…”

After a brief silence, Emlyn sighed silently.

Indeed. In the end, I have to face it myself and bear it.

This is the destiny of the messiah.

At the mention of the word “messiah,” Emlyn clearly smiled with a self-deprecating hint.

He then repeated inwardly, I can only rely on myself.

Just as this thought flashed through his mind, Father Utravsky’s voice sounded behind Emlyn.

“Time to set off.”

Emlyn turned his head and saw a huge sword on the back of the priest dressed in brown priest robes.

The sword’s length exceeded Emlyn’s height, and its width was close to his waist.

Together with Father Utravsky’s hill-like body, the terrifying pressure felt corporeal.

As a Sanguine Earl, Emlyn recovered from his stifled feeling and nodded gently.

“Okay.”

Today, they would head to the Southern Continent to participate in the besiegement of the Rose School of Thought.

Just as he replied, Emlyn suddenly recalled something and hurriedly said, “Wait for half a day.”

He wanted to gather most of the Sanguine in Backlund to discuss the pharmaceutical company.

Bishop Utravsky didn’t ask anything and nodded.

“Come find me when you’re ready.”

After watching Father Utravsky enter the depths of the cathedral, Emlyn turned his head to the Sanguine that were following him to the Southern Continent.

“Inform all the Sanguine in Backlund to come over. There’s something we need to discuss.”

“Yes, Lord Earl,” the Sanguine replied respectfully.

After they split up, Emlyn turned his head to look at the altar and the Sacred Emblem of Life in front of the cathedral. It was a simply drawn infant that was surrounded by symbols like wheat, flowers, spring water, and other symbols.

This made Emlyn’s thoughts suddenly turn adrift.

He had forgotten when he started spending less time in his bedroom, spending less time with his dolls. Even his hobby of studying history became more targeted and efficient.

This change didn’t take form in an instant. Instead, it was slowly formed over time. It was something that made it difficult for others to notice. By the time Emlyn discovered it, he had already adapted to this new life.

Emlyn retracted his gaze, raised his chin slightly, and shook his head with a smile.

This is the destiny of the messiah…